[
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"合格\"?",
    "word": "合格",
    "options": [
      "ごうかく",
      "とうけい",
      "にゅういん",
      "まんいん"
    ],
    "correct": "ごうかく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"解決\"?",
    "word": "解決",
    "options": [
      "かいけつ",
      "ていしゅつ",
      "きょうつう",
      "しばふ"
    ],
    "correct": "かいけつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"許可\"?",
    "word": "許可",
    "options": [
      "きょか",
      "うで",
      "ゆうがい",
      "じゅんじょ"
    ],
    "correct": "きょか"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"各自\"?",
    "word": "各自",
    "options": [
      "ひつじゅひん",
      "かくじ",
      "そんがい",
      "けってい"
    ],
    "correct": "かくじ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"拡大\"?",
    "word": "拡大",
    "options": [
      "ゆうれい",
      "かさなる",
      "ろんそう",
      "かくだい"
    ],
    "correct": "かくだい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"寄付\"?",
    "word": "寄付",
    "options": [
      "きふ",
      "ふきん",
      "こうか",
      "きわめて"
    ],
    "correct": "きふ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"技術\"?",
    "word": "技術",
    "options": [
      "ぎじゅつ",
      "きふ",
      "きざむ",
      "びよう"
    ],
    "correct": "ぎじゅつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"給与\"?",
    "word": "給与",
    "options": [
      "ちょうさ",
      "かかり",
      "みんよう",
      "きゅうよ"
    ],
    "correct": "きゅうよ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"共通\"?",
    "word": "共通",
    "options": [
      "ほうそう",
      "きょうつう",
      "こんごう",
      "くれる"
    ],
    "correct": "きょうつう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"協力\"?",
    "word": "協力",
    "options": [
      "きょうりょく",
      "ふそく",
      "ひかく",
      "きまり"
    ],
    "correct": "きょうりょく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"記録\"?",
    "word": "記録",
    "options": [
      "きろく",
      "もどる",
      "つかまる",
      "ちょきん"
    ],
    "correct": "きろく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"経営\"?",
    "word": "経営",
    "options": [
      "われわれ",
      "はらいもどす",
      "ぶき",
      "けいえい"
    ],
    "correct": "けいえい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"結果\"?",
    "word": "結果",
    "options": [
      "わざと",
      "めぐまれる",
      "こうこく",
      "けっか"
    ],
    "correct": "けっか"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"欠点\"?",
    "word": "欠点",
    "options": [
      "かくじつ",
      "けってん",
      "ぶんせき",
      "かんり"
    ],
    "correct": "けってん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"件名\"?",
    "word": "件名",
    "options": [
      "けんめい",
      "きょうか",
      "ばめん",
      "おうえん"
    ],
    "correct": "けんめい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"広告\"?",
    "word": "広告",
    "options": [
      "こうこく",
      "きょうふ",
      "やくわり",
      "きゅうそく"
    ],
    "correct": "こうこく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"構成\"?",
    "word": "構成",
    "options": [
      "こうせい",
      "よげん",
      "とどける",
      "はく"
    ],
    "correct": "こうせい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"行動\"?",
    "word": "行動",
    "options": [
      "せんでん",
      "こうどう",
      "きこう",
      "ちきゅう"
    ],
    "correct": "こうどう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"公務員\"?",
    "word": "公務員",
    "options": [
      "ごうかく",
      "さめる",
      "せきにん",
      "こうむいん"
    ],
    "correct": "こうむいん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"国際\"?",
    "word": "国際",
    "options": [
      "ちょくせつ",
      "さっか",
      "こくさい",
      "ひょうめん"
    ],
    "correct": "こくさい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"裁判\"?",
    "word": "裁判",
    "options": [
      "どういつ",
      "さいばん",
      "ふたん",
      "かたい"
    ],
    "correct": "さいばん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"材料\"?",
    "word": "材料",
    "options": [
      "ざいりょう",
      "せんもん",
      "きんにく",
      "かう"
    ],
    "correct": "ざいりょう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"産業\"?",
    "word": "産業",
    "options": [
      "ていし",
      "きふ",
      "めいしん",
      "さんぎょう"
    ],
    "correct": "さんぎょう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"賛成\"?",
    "word": "賛成",
    "options": [
      "さんせい",
      "ひょうばん",
      "とうめい",
      "むり"
    ],
    "correct": "さんせい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"支出\"?",
    "word": "支出",
    "options": [
      "びよう",
      "みとめる",
      "ししゅつ",
      "ごがく"
    ],
    "correct": "ししゅつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"事情\"?",
    "word": "事情",
    "options": [
      "じじょう",
      "ものがたり",
      "よさん",
      "こんらん"
    ],
    "correct": "じじょう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"実績\"?",
    "word": "実績",
    "options": [
      "わかれ",
      "もえる",
      "じっせき",
      "さす"
    ],
    "correct": "じっせき"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"支店\"?",
    "word": "支店",
    "options": [
      "もじ",
      "しょうがい",
      "ほうそう",
      "してん"
    ],
    "correct": "してん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"支配\"?",
    "word": "支配",
    "options": [
      "けってん",
      "さゆう",
      "しはい",
      "ひじょう"
    ],
    "correct": "しはい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"資格\"?",
    "word": "資格",
    "options": [
      "きざむ",
      "きぼう",
      "ごうけい",
      "しかく"
    ],
    "correct": "しかく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"氏名\"?",
    "word": "氏名",
    "options": [
      "してん",
      "きげん",
      "しめい",
      "すうじ"
    ],
    "correct": "しめい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"社会\"?",
    "word": "社会",
    "options": [
      "さばく",
      "しゃかい",
      "りゅうこう",
      "はっせい"
    ],
    "correct": "しゃかい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"車庫\"?",
    "word": "車庫",
    "options": [
      "しゃこ",
      "やくわり",
      "くさい",
      "ふる"
    ],
    "correct": "しゃこ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"修正\"?",
    "word": "修正",
    "options": [
      "くべつ",
      "ちょくせつ",
      "れんごう",
      "しゅうせい"
    ],
    "correct": "しゅうせい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"就職\"?",
    "word": "就職",
    "options": [
      "ひかく",
      "みょうじ",
      "しゅうしょく",
      "ふはい"
    ],
    "correct": "しゅうしょく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"集中\"?",
    "word": "集中",
    "options": [
      "めんどう",
      "はんい",
      "ろくおん",
      "しゅうちゅう"
    ],
    "correct": "しゅうちゅう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"証明\"?",
    "word": "証明",
    "options": [
      "しょくぎょう",
      "しょうめい",
      "きおく",
      "ゆうしょう"
    ],
    "correct": "しょうめい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"承認\"?",
    "word": "承認",
    "options": [
      "ぎゃく",
      "はら",
      "みかた",
      "しょうにん"
    ],
    "correct": "しょうにん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"職業\"?",
    "word": "職業",
    "options": [
      "しめる",
      "ぶんけん",
      "ひかく",
      "しょくぎょう"
    ],
    "correct": "しょくぎょう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"職場\"?",
    "word": "職場",
    "options": [
      "はんだん",
      "しょくば",
      "じじつ",
      "けしょう"
    ],
    "correct": "しょくば"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"審判\"?",
    "word": "審判",
    "options": [
      "しんぱん",
      "しめる",
      "じしゃく",
      "おえる"
    ],
    "correct": "しんぱん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"信頼\"?",
    "word": "信頼",
    "options": [
      "ひっき",
      "よげん",
      "しんらい",
      "せきにん"
    ],
    "correct": "しんらい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"制度\"?",
    "word": "制度",
    "options": [
      "ささえる",
      "せいど",
      "あこがれる",
      "こな"
    ],
    "correct": "せいど"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"製品\"?",
    "word": "製品",
    "options": [
      "おる",
      "しゅうしょく",
      "けんさ",
      "せいひん"
    ],
    "correct": "せいひん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"性能\"?",
    "word": "性能",
    "options": [
      "こんらん",
      "ていしゅつ",
      "けつろん",
      "せいのう"
    ],
    "correct": "せいのう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"設備\"?",
    "word": "設備",
    "options": [
      "ほしょう",
      "つうち",
      "りゃくす",
      "せつび"
    ],
    "correct": "せつび"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"選挙\"?",
    "word": "選挙",
    "options": [
      "せんきょ",
      "きよい",
      "めいかく",
      "ふくざつ"
    ],
    "correct": "せんきょ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"組織\"?",
    "word": "組織",
    "options": [
      "そしき",
      "さめる",
      "くさる",
      "ちゅうし"
    ],
    "correct": "そしき"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"損害\"?",
    "word": "損害",
    "options": [
      "そんがい",
      "ちょくせつ",
      "ぶんかい",
      "こくふく"
    ],
    "correct": "そんがい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"退職\"?",
    "word": "退職",
    "options": [
      "びよう",
      "おえる",
      "たいしょく",
      "れつ"
    ],
    "correct": "たいしょく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"態度\"?",
    "word": "態度",
    "options": [
      "きぼう",
      "たいど",
      "ふきゅう",
      "やっかい"
    ],
    "correct": "たいど"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"代表\"?",
    "word": "代表",
    "options": [
      "じじょう",
      "だいひょう",
      "きんゆう",
      "ぎゃく"
    ],
    "correct": "だいひょう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"担当\"?",
    "word": "担当",
    "options": [
      "たんとう",
      "きょうふ",
      "しゅうしょく",
      "はら"
    ],
    "correct": "たんとう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"地域\"?",
    "word": "地域",
    "options": [
      "けいい",
      "きょうりょく",
      "ちいき",
      "こうむいん"
    ],
    "correct": "ちいき"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"知識\"?",
    "word": "知識",
    "options": [
      "けいえい",
      "きょだい",
      "ちしき",
      "ゆにゅう"
    ],
    "correct": "ちしき"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"中央\"?",
    "word": "中央",
    "options": [
      "ちゅうおう",
      "ないよう",
      "りょうこう",
      "ぶっしつ"
    ],
    "correct": "ちゅうおう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"中止\"?",
    "word": "中止",
    "options": [
      "ゆそう",
      "こくふく",
      "さめる",
      "ちゅうし"
    ],
    "correct": "ちゅうし"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"貯金\"?",
    "word": "貯金",
    "options": [
      "まさつ",
      "こううん",
      "ちょきん",
      "かいてき"
    ],
    "correct": "ちょきん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"直接\"?",
    "word": "直接",
    "options": [
      "ちょくせつ",
      "うやまう",
      "うらぎる",
      "かよう"
    ],
    "correct": "ちょくせつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"通知\"?",
    "word": "通知",
    "options": [
      "すぐれる",
      "ほうほう",
      "こてい",
      "つうち"
    ],
    "correct": "つうち"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"提案\"?",
    "word": "提案",
    "options": [
      "ていあん",
      "しゃかい",
      "げいじゅつ",
      "てきよう"
    ],
    "correct": "ていあん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"適当\"?",
    "word": "適当",
    "options": [
      "てきとう",
      "ほうもん",
      "こんごう",
      "ひとこと"
    ],
    "correct": "てきとう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"適用\"?",
    "word": "適用",
    "options": [
      "てきよう",
      "かって",
      "しげん",
      "きょうふ"
    ],
    "correct": "てきよう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"展覧会\"?",
    "word": "展覧会",
    "options": [
      "てんらんかい",
      "ぶんせき",
      "せんもん",
      "きょうふ"
    ],
    "correct": "てんらんかい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"統計\"?",
    "word": "統計",
    "options": [
      "かがやく",
      "ていし",
      "かくす",
      "とうけい"
    ],
    "correct": "とうけい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"投資\"?",
    "word": "投資",
    "options": [
      "はく",
      "しゅちょう",
      "とうし",
      "ふつう"
    ],
    "correct": "とうし"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"努力\"?",
    "word": "努力",
    "options": [
      "こうほ",
      "どりょく",
      "おえる",
      "かよう"
    ],
    "correct": "どりょく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"内容\"?",
    "word": "内容",
    "options": [
      "かくだい",
      "きゅう",
      "ないよう",
      "ひょうか"
    ],
    "correct": "ないよう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"農業\"?",
    "word": "農業",
    "options": [
      "しゅうかく",
      "せいけつ",
      "のうぎょう",
      "ひっき"
    ],
    "correct": "のうぎょう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"能率\"?",
    "word": "能率",
    "options": [
      "どくとく",
      "けんきょ",
      "はっこう",
      "のうりつ"
    ],
    "correct": "のうりつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"範囲\"?",
    "word": "範囲",
    "options": [
      "はんい",
      "けん",
      "くさる",
      "ぎじゅつ"
    ],
    "correct": "はんい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"犯罪\"?",
    "word": "犯罪",
    "options": [
      "はんざい",
      "しょうひ",
      "てきよう",
      "どりょく"
    ],
    "correct": "はんざい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"比較\"?",
    "word": "比較",
    "options": [
      "てきとう",
      "へんさい",
      "よろこび",
      "ひかく"
    ],
    "correct": "ひかく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"評価\"?",
    "word": "評価",
    "options": [
      "ふる",
      "ひょうか",
      "みんよう",
      "さまざま"
    ],
    "correct": "ひょうか"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"平等\"?",
    "word": "平等",
    "options": [
      "びょうどう",
      "こおる",
      "さいこう",
      "けんめい"
    ],
    "correct": "びょうどう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"普及\"?",
    "word": "普及",
    "options": [
      "ひてい",
      "やちん",
      "ふきゅう",
      "むじゅん"
    ],
    "correct": "ふきゅう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"複雑\"?",
    "word": "複雑",
    "options": [
      "こんやく",
      "しめる",
      "きよい",
      "ふくざつ"
    ],
    "correct": "ふくざつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"物質\"?",
    "word": "物質",
    "options": [
      "ぶっしつ",
      "よゆう",
      "さいてい",
      "びよう"
    ],
    "correct": "ぶっしつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"返済\"?",
    "word": "返済",
    "options": [
      "へんさい",
      "かのうせい",
      "せいふ",
      "じゅんじょ"
    ],
    "correct": "へんさい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"報告\"?",
    "word": "報告",
    "options": [
      "ひこう",
      "むすこ",
      "おそろしい",
      "ほうこく"
    ],
    "correct": "ほうこく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"方法\"?",
    "word": "方法",
    "options": [
      "たいわ",
      "ほうほう",
      "けいえい",
      "せいちょう"
    ],
    "correct": "ほうほう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"訪問\"?",
    "word": "訪問",
    "options": [
      "せいちょう",
      "げき",
      "ほうもん",
      "やちん"
    ],
    "correct": "ほうもん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"満足\"?",
    "word": "満足",
    "options": [
      "おもいで",
      "りこう",
      "しげん",
      "まんぞく"
    ],
    "correct": "まんぞく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"名字\"?",
    "word": "名字",
    "options": [
      "きょういく",
      "みなと",
      "せんもん",
      "みょうじ"
    ],
    "correct": "みょうじ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"命令\"?",
    "word": "命令",
    "options": [
      "めいれい",
      "わだい",
      "かって",
      "かいせつ"
    ],
    "correct": "めいれい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"目的\"?",
    "word": "目的",
    "options": [
      "もくてき",
      "よごれ",
      "かいせつ",
      "けんり"
    ],
    "correct": "もくてき"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"予算\"?",
    "word": "予算",
    "options": [
      "ふどうさん",
      "よさん",
      "めいわく",
      "かくじつ"
    ],
    "correct": "よさん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"離婚\"?",
    "word": "離婚",
    "options": [
      "ちょきん",
      "そうとう",
      "こんごう",
      "りこん"
    ],
    "correct": "りこん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"理想\"?",
    "word": "理想",
    "options": [
      "にっき",
      "りそう",
      "よごれる",
      "かいてき"
    ],
    "correct": "りそう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"利益\"?",
    "word": "利益",
    "options": [
      "りえき",
      "さけぶ",
      "くんれん",
      "よゆう"
    ],
    "correct": "りえき"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"例外\"?",
    "word": "例外",
    "options": [
      "れいがい",
      "さかい",
      "こんやく",
      "やちん"
    ],
    "correct": "れいがい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"連合\"?",
    "word": "連合",
    "options": [
      "じゅうみん",
      "れいぎ",
      "こうぎ",
      "れんごう"
    ],
    "correct": "れんごう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"愛用\"?",
    "word": "愛用",
    "options": [
      "ほうりつ",
      "ゆるす",
      "きねん",
      "あいよう"
    ],
    "correct": "あいよう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"飽きる\"?",
    "word": "飽きる",
    "options": [
      "きょうかい",
      "よゆう",
      "ふきゅう",
      "あきる"
    ],
    "correct": "あきる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"握手\"?",
    "word": "握手",
    "options": [
      "よごれ",
      "ろうご",
      "あくしゅ",
      "ゆそう"
    ],
    "correct": "あくしゅ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"憧れる\"?",
    "word": "憧れる",
    "options": [
      "あこがれる",
      "かいぜん",
      "じゅんじょ",
      "さっか"
    ],
    "correct": "あこがれる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"厚かましい\"?",
    "word": "厚かましい",
    "options": [
      "やくだつ",
      "りゅうこう",
      "あつかましい",
      "さいばん"
    ],
    "correct": "あつかましい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"怪しい\"?",
    "word": "怪しい",
    "options": [
      "ていし",
      "はんだん",
      "さそう",
      "あやしい"
    ],
    "correct": "あやしい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"荒い\"?",
    "word": "荒い",
    "options": [
      "かかり",
      "ちゅうせん",
      "さっきょく",
      "あらい"
    ],
    "correct": "あらい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"争う\"?",
    "word": "争う",
    "options": [
      "うで",
      "ゆそう",
      "うつる",
      "あらそう"
    ],
    "correct": "あらそう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"慌てる\"?",
    "word": "慌てる",
    "options": [
      "あわてる",
      "くみたてる",
      "かせぐ",
      "こんざつ"
    ],
    "correct": "あわてる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"意識\"?",
    "word": "意識",
    "options": [
      "いしき",
      "ひょうめん",
      "さいしょ",
      "とむ"
    ],
    "correct": "いしき"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"慰める\"?",
    "word": "慰める",
    "options": [
      "なぐさめる",
      "げき",
      "ちょきん",
      "はくぶつかん"
    ],
    "correct": "なぐさめる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"伺う\"?",
    "word": "伺う",
    "options": [
      "しょうにん",
      "うかがう",
      "きゅうよ",
      "くんれん"
    ],
    "correct": "うかがう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"疑う\"?",
    "word": "疑う",
    "options": [
      "うたがう",
      "ちえ",
      "こてい",
      "ゆうめい"
    ],
    "correct": "うたがう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"敬う\"?",
    "word": "敬う",
    "options": [
      "うやまう",
      "ぶっしつ",
      "さいしょ",
      "つうち"
    ],
    "correct": "うやまう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"恨む\"?",
    "word": "恨む",
    "options": [
      "うらむ",
      "そんけい",
      "さかい",
      "せいちょう"
    ],
    "correct": "うらむ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"羨ましい\"?",
    "word": "羨ましい",
    "options": [
      "きんゆう",
      "うらやましい",
      "めいかく",
      "うったえる"
    ],
    "correct": "うらやましい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"影響\"?",
    "word": "影響",
    "options": [
      "りゃくす",
      "えいきょう",
      "へんか",
      "もうしこむ"
    ],
    "correct": "えいきょう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"演奏\"?",
    "word": "演奏",
    "options": [
      "えんそう",
      "きんにく",
      "しゅうちゅう",
      "ほんかく"
    ],
    "correct": "えんそう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"遠慮\"?",
    "word": "遠慮",
    "options": [
      "やとう",
      "ぎむ",
      "しょうめい",
      "えんりょ"
    ],
    "correct": "えんりょ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"追い越す\"?",
    "word": "追い越す",
    "options": [
      "げんさん",
      "おいこす",
      "けんとう",
      "ぶんかい"
    ],
    "correct": "おいこす"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"応援\"?",
    "word": "応援",
    "options": [
      "おうえん",
      "ゆうがい",
      "れいとう",
      "つうち"
    ],
    "correct": "おうえん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"王様\"?",
    "word": "王様",
    "options": [
      "ゆにゅう",
      "おうさま",
      "ちょくせつ",
      "さんぽ"
    ],
    "correct": "おうさま"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"惜しい\"?",
    "word": "惜しい",
    "options": [
      "そうだん",
      "ぜったい",
      "さくじょ",
      "おしい"
    ],
    "correct": "おしい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"恐ろしい\"?",
    "word": "恐ろしい",
    "options": [
      "きこう",
      "こうむいん",
      "まねく",
      "おそろしい"
    ],
    "correct": "おそろしい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"落ち着く\"?",
    "word": "落ち着く",
    "options": [
      "おちつく",
      "こううん",
      "はなれる",
      "りゃくす"
    ],
    "correct": "おちつく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"思い出\"?",
    "word": "思い出",
    "options": [
      "ごがく",
      "ひんしつ",
      "おもいで",
      "ほうりつ"
    ],
    "correct": "おもいで"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"快晴\"?",
    "word": "快晴",
    "options": [
      "さばく",
      "えがく",
      "けいい",
      "かいせい"
    ],
    "correct": "かいせい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"解説\"?",
    "word": "解説",
    "options": [
      "さい",
      "かいせつ",
      "うやまう",
      "しあわせ"
    ],
    "correct": "かいせつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"改善\"?",
    "word": "改善",
    "options": [
      "きゅうよ",
      "しゅうちゅう",
      "はく",
      "かいぜん"
    ],
    "correct": "かいぜん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"快適\"?",
    "word": "快適",
    "options": [
      "かいてき",
      "やくわり",
      "くさい",
      "ちしき"
    ],
    "correct": "かいてき"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"回復\"?",
    "word": "回復",
    "options": [
      "かいてき",
      "かいふく",
      "けんり",
      "けしき"
    ],
    "correct": "かいふく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"飼う\"?",
    "word": "飼う",
    "options": [
      "はいふ",
      "かう",
      "さいしん",
      "しやくしょ"
    ],
    "correct": "かう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"抱える\"?",
    "word": "抱える",
    "options": [
      "かかえる",
      "ゆうめい",
      "へんか",
      "けんとう"
    ],
    "correct": "かかえる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"価格\"?",
    "word": "価格",
    "options": [
      "さんこう",
      "しょうがくきん",
      "ゆそう",
      "かかく"
    ],
    "correct": "かかく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"輝く\"?",
    "word": "輝く",
    "options": [
      "かがやく",
      "まるい",
      "やちん",
      "こうぞう"
    ],
    "correct": "かがやく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"係\"?",
    "word": "係",
    "options": [
      "かかり",
      "とうめい",
      "おそれる",
      "きょうりょく"
    ],
    "correct": "かかり"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"限る\"?",
    "word": "限る",
    "options": [
      "せんしゅ",
      "さまざま",
      "さ",
      "かぎる"
    ],
    "correct": "かぎる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"覚悟\"?",
    "word": "覚悟",
    "options": [
      "かくご",
      "さつ",
      "ぶっしつ",
      "きゅうよ"
    ],
    "correct": "かくご"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"確実\"?",
    "word": "確実",
    "options": [
      "かくじつ",
      "ゆうせん",
      "つうよう",
      "ゆうせん"
    ],
    "correct": "かくじつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"確認\"?",
    "word": "確認",
    "options": [
      "じっせき",
      "きらう",
      "かくにん",
      "きみょう"
    ],
    "correct": "かくにん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"隠す\"?",
    "word": "隠す",
    "options": [
      "ぶんめい",
      "こしょう",
      "かくす",
      "かくじ"
    ],
    "correct": "かくす"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"過去\"?",
    "word": "過去",
    "options": [
      "かこ",
      "くべつ",
      "げんだい",
      "こうか"
    ],
    "correct": "かこ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"重なる\"?",
    "word": "重なる",
    "options": [
      "かさなる",
      "そうだん",
      "ほうもん",
      "ざいりょう"
    ],
    "correct": "かさなる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"飾り\"?",
    "word": "飾り",
    "options": [
      "はんい",
      "かざり",
      "すぐれる",
      "ごうかく"
    ],
    "correct": "かざり"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"稼ぐ\"?",
    "word": "稼ぐ",
    "options": [
      "ぶんせき",
      "せんもん",
      "へいきん",
      "かせぐ"
    ],
    "correct": "かせぐ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"数える\"?",
    "word": "数える",
    "options": [
      "てきとう",
      "かぞえる",
      "きらう",
      "わざと"
    ],
    "correct": "かぞえる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"固い\"?",
    "word": "固い",
    "options": [
      "おくる",
      "かたい",
      "せいちょう",
      "ようき"
    ],
    "correct": "かたい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"勝手\"?",
    "word": "勝手",
    "options": [
      "かって",
      "およぶ",
      "りそう",
      "かくじ"
    ],
    "correct": "かって"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"悲しむ\"?",
    "word": "悲しむ",
    "options": [
      "こうどう",
      "さい",
      "やっかい",
      "かなしむ"
    ],
    "correct": "かなしむ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"可能性\"?",
    "word": "可能性",
    "options": [
      "きょうふ",
      "げんかい",
      "かいぜん",
      "かのうせい"
    ],
    "correct": "かのうせい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"我慢\"?",
    "word": "我慢",
    "options": [
      "しゃかい",
      "がまん",
      "じょうけん",
      "ふたん"
    ],
    "correct": "がまん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"髪型\"?",
    "word": "髪型",
    "options": [
      "せいさく",
      "かみがた",
      "すぐれる",
      "ふっかつ"
    ],
    "correct": "かみがた"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"通う\"?",
    "word": "通う",
    "options": [
      "れいせい",
      "みつど",
      "かよう",
      "さいぜん"
    ],
    "correct": "かよう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"からかう\"?",
    "word": "からかう",
    "options": [
      "さゆう",
      "からかう",
      "せんきょ",
      "こきゅう"
    ],
    "correct": "からかう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"軽い\"?",
    "word": "軽い",
    "options": [
      "かるい",
      "まよう",
      "ゆにゅう",
      "もえる"
    ],
    "correct": "かるい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"可愛がる\"?",
    "word": "可愛がる",
    "options": [
      "おぎなう",
      "ぎいん",
      "かわいがる",
      "かくす"
    ],
    "correct": "かわいがる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"乾かす\"?",
    "word": "乾かす",
    "options": [
      "かわかす",
      "かいてき",
      "かえる",
      "やちん"
    ],
    "correct": "かわかす"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"代わりに\"?",
    "word": "代わりに",
    "options": [
      "かわりに",
      "りかい",
      "きゅうそく",
      "ちつじょ"
    ],
    "correct": "かわりに"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"感動\"?",
    "word": "感動",
    "options": [
      "かんどう",
      "おちつく",
      "きぼう",
      "りえき"
    ],
    "correct": "かんどう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"管理\"?",
    "word": "管理",
    "options": [
      "かんり",
      "きんにく",
      "わ",
      "ししゅつ"
    ],
    "correct": "かんり"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"完了\"?",
    "word": "完了",
    "options": [
      "ほうそく",
      "こし",
      "れいせい",
      "かんりょう"
    ],
    "correct": "かんりょう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"関連\"?",
    "word": "関連",
    "options": [
      "ほうそく",
      "きかい",
      "こううん",
      "かんれん"
    ],
    "correct": "かんれん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"議員\"?",
    "word": "議員",
    "options": [
      "げんじょう",
      "とじる",
      "せんきょ",
      "ぎいん"
    ],
    "correct": "ぎいん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"記憶\"?",
    "word": "記憶",
    "options": [
      "じっさい",
      "みちびく",
      "きおく",
      "もんく"
    ],
    "correct": "きおく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"気温\"?",
    "word": "気温",
    "options": [
      "きおん",
      "ようぼう",
      "いちにんしょう",
      "せいしつ"
    ],
    "correct": "きおん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"機会\"?",
    "word": "機会",
    "options": [
      "けっかん",
      "ほうりつ",
      "てきとう",
      "きかい"
    ],
    "correct": "きかい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"期限\"?",
    "word": "期限",
    "options": [
      "きげん",
      "やとう",
      "しずむ",
      "かよう"
    ],
    "correct": "きげん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"気候\"?",
    "word": "気候",
    "options": [
      "とらえる",
      "つかまる",
      "こうかん",
      "きこう"
    ],
    "correct": "きこう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"刻む\"?",
    "word": "刻む",
    "options": [
      "きざむ",
      "けんとう",
      "ていあん",
      "わん"
    ],
    "correct": "きざむ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"儀式\"?",
    "word": "儀式",
    "options": [
      "ぎしき",
      "まよう",
      "きおく",
      "さいじつ"
    ],
    "correct": "ぎしき"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"期待\"?",
    "word": "期待",
    "options": [
      "きたい",
      "おうえん",
      "りそう",
      "せいさく"
    ],
    "correct": "きたい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"貴重\"?",
    "word": "貴重",
    "options": [
      "きちょう",
      "ぶっしつ",
      "ふよう",
      "おそろしい"
    ],
    "correct": "きちょう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"寄付\"?",
    "word": "寄付",
    "options": [
      "きふ",
      "こううん",
      "きょうふ",
      "かう"
    ],
    "correct": "きふ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"希望\"?",
    "word": "希望",
    "options": [
      "きぼう",
      "うやまう",
      "てんこう",
      "やとう"
    ],
    "correct": "きぼう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"決まり\"?",
    "word": "決まり",
    "options": [
      "きまり",
      "せいひん",
      "せいちょう",
      "もうしこむ"
    ],
    "correct": "きまり"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"気味\"?",
    "word": "気味",
    "options": [
      "ぎみ",
      "さいぜん",
      "こううん",
      "きゅうよ"
    ],
    "correct": "ぎみ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"教育\"?",
    "word": "教育",
    "options": [
      "きょういく",
      "さそう",
      "せいり",
      "こうさい"
    ],
    "correct": "きょういく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"教科書\"?",
    "word": "教科書",
    "options": [
      "けんとう",
      "ひかく",
      "きょうかしょ",
      "こうこう"
    ],
    "correct": "きょうかしょ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"競技\"?",
    "word": "競技",
    "options": [
      "きょうぎ",
      "はったつ",
      "かくご",
      "あらい"
    ],
    "correct": "きょうぎ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"行事\"?",
    "word": "行事",
    "options": [
      "ぐんたい",
      "じゅんじょ",
      "ぎょうじ",
      "きぼう"
    ],
    "correct": "ぎょうじ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"恐怖\"?",
    "word": "恐怖",
    "options": [
      "もくてき",
      "しゅうしょく",
      "きょうふ",
      "はんだん"
    ],
    "correct": "きょうふ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"許可\"?",
    "word": "許可",
    "options": [
      "げんそく",
      "おぎなう",
      "きょか",
      "たいど"
    ],
    "correct": "きょか"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"巨大\"?",
    "word": "巨大",
    "options": [
      "ぎゃく",
      "しゅび",
      "れんぞく",
      "きょだい"
    ],
    "correct": "きょだい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"嫌う\"?",
    "word": "嫌う",
    "options": [
      "ふっかつ",
      "かぞえる",
      "きらう",
      "きよう"
    ],
    "correct": "きらう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"霧\"?",
    "word": "霧",
    "options": [
      "きり",
      "えがく",
      "とうし",
      "せいさく"
    ],
    "correct": "きり"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"緊張\"?",
    "word": "緊張",
    "options": [
      "ほうふ",
      "きんちょう",
      "びよう",
      "べんとう"
    ],
    "correct": "きんちょう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"筋肉\"?",
    "word": "筋肉",
    "options": [
      "こじん",
      "きんにく",
      "まるい",
      "てきよう"
    ],
    "correct": "きんにく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"具合\"?",
    "word": "具合",
    "options": [
      "きちょう",
      "うたがう",
      "ぐあい",
      "げんじょう"
    ],
    "correct": "ぐあい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"臭い\"?",
    "word": "臭い",
    "options": [
      "くさい",
      "はっけん",
      "ゆうめい",
      "どうとく"
    ],
    "correct": "くさい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"腐る\"?",
    "word": "腐る",
    "options": [
      "せいひん",
      "くんれん",
      "かせぐ",
      "くさる"
    ],
    "correct": "くさる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"苦労\"?",
    "word": "苦労",
    "options": [
      "くろう",
      "ちゅうい",
      "てつ",
      "わりびき"
    ],
    "correct": "くろう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"詳しい\"?",
    "word": "詳しい",
    "options": [
      "ていしゅつ",
      "くわしい",
      "しめる",
      "かさなる"
    ],
    "correct": "くわしい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"訓練\"?",
    "word": "訓練",
    "options": [
      "かいせつ",
      "こきゅう",
      "せいひん",
      "くんれん"
    ],
    "correct": "くんれん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"敬意\"?",
    "word": "敬意",
    "options": [
      "しゃこ",
      "かがやく",
      "とうし",
      "けいい"
    ],
    "correct": "けいい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"景気\"?",
    "word": "景気",
    "options": [
      "はかる",
      "げんさん",
      "さわる",
      "けいき"
    ],
    "correct": "けいき"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"景色\"?",
    "word": "景色",
    "options": [
      "けしき",
      "よゆう",
      "こうか",
      "きぼう"
    ],
    "correct": "けしき"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"化粧\"?",
    "word": "化粧",
    "options": [
      "けしょう",
      "ゆうせん",
      "こうさい",
      "どりょく"
    ],
    "correct": "けしょう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"結果\"?",
    "word": "結果",
    "options": [
      "ぶんかい",
      "けっか",
      "ひにく",
      "てんさい"
    ],
    "correct": "けっか"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"欠陥\"?",
    "word": "欠陥",
    "options": [
      "ひじょう",
      "きずく",
      "ちきゅう",
      "けっかん"
    ],
    "correct": "けっかん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"決心\"?",
    "word": "決心",
    "options": [
      "かざる",
      "けっしん",
      "ぬく",
      "こんやく"
    ],
    "correct": "けっしん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"欠席\"?",
    "word": "欠席",
    "options": [
      "はげしい",
      "ほうもん",
      "さそう",
      "けっせき"
    ],
    "correct": "けっせき"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"決定\"?",
    "word": "決定",
    "options": [
      "はんざい",
      "よくばり",
      "こんらん",
      "けってい"
    ],
    "correct": "けってい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"限界\"?",
    "word": "限界",
    "options": [
      "げんかい",
      "ことば",
      "せいしつ",
      "さ"
    ],
    "correct": "げんかい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"現金\"?",
    "word": "現金",
    "options": [
      "とらえる",
      "げんきん",
      "しだい",
      "まよう"
    ],
    "correct": "げんきん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"健康\"?",
    "word": "健康",
    "options": [
      "あわてる",
      "くみたてる",
      "けんこう",
      "はんだん"
    ],
    "correct": "けんこう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"検査\"?",
    "word": "検査",
    "options": [
      "おもいで",
      "ふくらむ",
      "うやまう",
      "けんさ"
    ],
    "correct": "けんさ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"建設\"?",
    "word": "建設",
    "options": [
      "しつど",
      "しょくぎょう",
      "つうち",
      "けんせつ"
    ],
    "correct": "けんせつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"謙遜\"?",
    "word": "謙遜",
    "options": [
      "けんそん",
      "ていしゅつ",
      "はっそう",
      "ゆうり"
    ],
    "correct": "けんそん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"検討\"?",
    "word": "検討",
    "options": [
      "ろんぶん",
      "けんとう",
      "あきる",
      "さいてい"
    ],
    "correct": "けんとう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"権利\"?",
    "word": "権利",
    "options": [
      "けんり",
      "おもいで",
      "てきよう",
      "かくじ"
    ],
    "correct": "けんり"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"恋人\"?",
    "word": "恋人",
    "options": [
      "こいびと",
      "めんぜい",
      "あつかましい",
      "わかれ"
    ],
    "correct": "こいびと"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"幸運\"?",
    "word": "幸運",
    "options": [
      "こううん",
      "さわる",
      "しょり",
      "よゆう"
    ],
    "correct": "こううん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"豪華\"?",
    "word": "豪華",
    "options": [
      "ごうか",
      "ゆずる",
      "びよう",
      "ふこう"
    ],
    "correct": "ごうか"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"交換\"?",
    "word": "交換",
    "options": [
      "ろくおん",
      "きずく",
      "こうかん",
      "しゅうちゅう"
    ],
    "correct": "こうかん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"合計\"?",
    "word": "合計",
    "options": [
      "ぎしき",
      "ごうけい",
      "うらむ",
      "きかい"
    ],
    "correct": "ごうけい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"講義\"?",
    "word": "講義",
    "options": [
      "こんなん",
      "ちょうさ",
      "こうぎ",
      "こおり"
    ],
    "correct": "こうぎ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"孝行\"?",
    "word": "孝行",
    "options": [
      "はんい",
      "かえる",
      "ひてい",
      "こうこう"
    ],
    "correct": "こうこう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"交際\"?",
    "word": "交際",
    "options": [
      "さいしょ",
      "きかい",
      "けんきょ",
      "こうさい"
    ],
    "correct": "こうさい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"交渉\"?",
    "word": "交渉",
    "options": [
      "こうしょう",
      "きんゆう",
      "てきよう",
      "もえる"
    ],
    "correct": "こうしょう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"構造\"?",
    "word": "構造",
    "options": [
      "ごうけい",
      "こうぞう",
      "どりょく",
      "ぜったい"
    ],
    "correct": "こうぞう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"幸福\"?",
    "word": "幸福",
    "options": [
      "ほしょう",
      "ごかい",
      "あやしい",
      "こうふく"
    ],
    "correct": "こうふく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"公平\"?",
    "word": "公平",
    "options": [
      "へんさい",
      "きゅうそく",
      "おちつく",
      "こうへい"
    ],
    "correct": "こうへい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"候補\"?",
    "word": "候補",
    "options": [
      "ひこう",
      "さいこう",
      "くわしい",
      "こうほ"
    ],
    "correct": "こうほ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"越える\"?",
    "word": "越える",
    "options": [
      "おどろかす",
      "けんさ",
      "こえる",
      "もくてき"
    ],
    "correct": "こえる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"氷\"?",
    "word": "氷",
    "options": [
      "こおり",
      "けってん",
      "きょか",
      "さいのう"
    ],
    "correct": "こおり"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"凍る\"?",
    "word": "凍る",
    "options": [
      "ふどうさん",
      "うたがう",
      "こおる",
      "きんちょう"
    ],
    "correct": "こおる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"誤解\"?",
    "word": "誤解",
    "options": [
      "つごう",
      "ふそく",
      "ごかい",
      "わん"
    ],
    "correct": "ごかい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"語学\"?",
    "word": "語学",
    "options": [
      "きらう",
      "つうち",
      "えんりょ",
      "ごがく"
    ],
    "correct": "ごがく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"呼吸\"?",
    "word": "呼吸",
    "options": [
      "ひょうめん",
      "さからう",
      "こきゅう",
      "ひとしい"
    ],
    "correct": "こきゅう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"克服\"?",
    "word": "克服",
    "options": [
      "ようりょう",
      "こくふく",
      "えがく",
      "へんか"
    ],
    "correct": "こくふく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"腰\"?",
    "word": "腰",
    "options": [
      "こし",
      "さわる",
      "ぶんけん",
      "きょだい"
    ],
    "correct": "こし"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"故障\"?",
    "word": "故障",
    "options": [
      "ほうもん",
      "そうさ",
      "こしょう",
      "しめる"
    ],
    "correct": "こしょう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"個人\"?",
    "word": "個人",
    "options": [
      "こじん",
      "こうこく",
      "しょくば",
      "めんぜい"
    ],
    "correct": "こじん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"言葉\"?",
    "word": "言葉",
    "options": [
      "ざいさん",
      "ひかく",
      "けつろん",
      "ことば"
    ],
    "correct": "ことば"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"断る\"?",
    "word": "断る",
    "options": [
      "きょういく",
      "けっか",
      "ざいさん",
      "ことわる"
    ],
    "correct": "ことわる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"粉\"?",
    "word": "粉",
    "options": [
      "けんさ",
      "こな",
      "かいせい",
      "さいご"
    ],
    "correct": "こな"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"好み\"?",
    "word": "好み",
    "options": [
      "このみ",
      "しょうめい",
      "ほうふ",
      "しゅび"
    ],
    "correct": "このみ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"混合\"?",
    "word": "混合",
    "options": [
      "こんごう",
      "すぐれる",
      "みちる",
      "かがやく"
    ],
    "correct": "こんごう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"婚約\"?",
    "word": "婚約",
    "options": [
      "こんやく",
      "ぶんしょう",
      "ろくおん",
      "あらそう"
    ],
    "correct": "こんやく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"混乱\"?",
    "word": "混乱",
    "options": [
      "こんらん",
      "ていど",
      "ぎじゅつ",
      "せいげん"
    ],
    "correct": "こんらん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"最初\"?",
    "word": "最初",
    "options": [
      "つかまる",
      "しょうにん",
      "ゆずる",
      "さいしょ"
    ],
    "correct": "さいしょ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"最後\"?",
    "word": "最後",
    "options": [
      "さいご",
      "ごうかく",
      "ひがい",
      "れいがい"
    ],
    "correct": "さいご"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"最高\"?",
    "word": "最高",
    "options": [
      "さいこう",
      "やちん",
      "そんけい",
      "さんこう"
    ],
    "correct": "さいこう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"最近\"?",
    "word": "最近",
    "options": [
      "ふきゅう",
      "けっせき",
      "さいきん",
      "ごうか"
    ],
    "correct": "さいきん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"財産\"?",
    "word": "財産",
    "options": [
      "せんきょ",
      "よくばり",
      "まんいん",
      "ざいさん"
    ],
    "correct": "ざいさん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"祭日\"?",
    "word": "祭日",
    "options": [
      "さいじつ",
      "うらやましい",
      "けってい",
      "あいよう"
    ],
    "correct": "さいじつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"採集\"?",
    "word": "採集",
    "options": [
      "さいしゅう",
      "やくわり",
      "しほう",
      "うたがう"
    ],
    "correct": "さいしゅう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"再生\"?",
    "word": "再生",
    "options": [
      "しめる",
      "れいたん",
      "さいせい",
      "げんそく"
    ],
    "correct": "さいせい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"最善\"?",
    "word": "最善",
    "options": [
      "みょうじ",
      "さいぜん",
      "ゆるす",
      "ちゅうい"
    ],
    "correct": "さいぜん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"最低\"?",
    "word": "最低",
    "options": [
      "さす",
      "さいてい",
      "じき",
      "どくとく"
    ],
    "correct": "さいてい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"才能\"?",
    "word": "才能",
    "options": [
      "さいのう",
      "ようりょう",
      "しゅえん",
      "ほうもん"
    ],
    "correct": "さいのう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"裁判\"?",
    "word": "裁判",
    "options": [
      "さいばん",
      "むじゅん",
      "ごうかく",
      "ほる"
    ],
    "correct": "さいばん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"境\"?",
    "word": "境",
    "options": [
      "さかい",
      "とうし",
      "きょうかい",
      "ほうもん"
    ],
    "correct": "さかい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"逆らう\"?",
    "word": "逆らう",
    "options": [
      "ようそ",
      "ざいさん",
      "さからう",
      "さまざま"
    ],
    "correct": "さからう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"盛り\"?",
    "word": "盛り",
    "options": [
      "しょうかい",
      "さかり",
      "のうぎょう",
      "はんにん"
    ],
    "correct": "さかり"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"叫ぶ\"?",
    "word": "叫ぶ",
    "options": [
      "みりょく",
      "さけぶ",
      "やちん",
      "びんぼう"
    ],
    "correct": "さけぶ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"避ける\"?",
    "word": "避ける",
    "options": [
      "はんい",
      "やくわり",
      "ふたん",
      "さける"
    ],
    "correct": "さける"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"支える\"?",
    "word": "支える",
    "options": [
      "ささえる",
      "はく",
      "こんらん",
      "のうりつ"
    ],
    "correct": "ささえる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"指す\"?",
    "word": "指す",
    "options": [
      "めいかく",
      "ようき",
      "しょうにん",
      "さす"
    ],
    "correct": "さす"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"誘う\"?",
    "word": "誘う",
    "options": [
      "わらい",
      "はたらく",
      "よゆう",
      "さそう"
    ],
    "correct": "さそう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"札\"?",
    "word": "札",
    "options": [
      "さつ",
      "とらえる",
      "きんちょう",
      "せきにん"
    ],
    "correct": "さつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"作家\"?",
    "word": "作家",
    "options": [
      "さっか",
      "せいちょう",
      "おうさま",
      "うで"
    ],
    "correct": "さっか"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"作曲\"?",
    "word": "作曲",
    "options": [
      "きんちょう",
      "どりょく",
      "しょうにん",
      "さっきょく"
    ],
    "correct": "さっきょく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"砂漠\"?",
    "word": "砂漠",
    "options": [
      "かくじ",
      "ていし",
      "さくせい",
      "さばく"
    ],
    "correct": "さばく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"差別\"?",
    "word": "差別",
    "options": [
      "さべつ",
      "はさむ",
      "ちゅうもく",
      "くつう"
    ],
    "correct": "さべつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"作法\"?",
    "word": "作法",
    "options": [
      "さほう",
      "にんずう",
      "まんいん",
      "わん"
    ],
    "correct": "さほう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"様々\"?",
    "word": "様々",
    "options": [
      "さまざま",
      "れいとう",
      "ばめん",
      "さほう"
    ],
    "correct": "さまざま"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"冷める\"?",
    "word": "冷める",
    "options": [
      "さめる",
      "ぶんめい",
      "まねく",
      "よろこび"
    ],
    "correct": "さめる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"覚める\"?",
    "word": "覚める",
    "options": [
      "きまり",
      "ひがえり",
      "かける",
      "さめる"
    ],
    "correct": "さめる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"去る\"?",
    "word": "去る",
    "options": [
      "さる",
      "ははおや",
      "ゆいいつ",
      "かぶる"
    ],
    "correct": "さる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"参加\"?",
    "word": "参加",
    "options": [
      "さんか",
      "へんこう",
      "きげん",
      "さいきん"
    ],
    "correct": "さんか"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"参考\"?",
    "word": "参考",
    "options": [
      "さんこう",
      "とうけい",
      "さいのう",
      "さらなる"
    ],
    "correct": "さんこう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"賛成\"?",
    "word": "賛成",
    "options": [
      "しゅうかく",
      "しゃこ",
      "りつ",
      "さんせい"
    ],
    "correct": "さんせい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"散歩\"?",
    "word": "散歩",
    "options": [
      "かなしむ",
      "うで",
      "さんぽ",
      "けんとう"
    ],
    "correct": "さんぽ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"幸せ\"?",
    "word": "幸せ",
    "options": [
      "つうち",
      "りこん",
      "しあわせ",
      "せいしつ"
    ],
    "correct": "しあわせ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"時期\"?",
    "word": "時期",
    "options": [
      "じき",
      "ふつう",
      "かんどう",
      "きゅうそく"
    ],
    "correct": "じき"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"刺激\"?",
    "word": "刺激",
    "options": [
      "さいご",
      "へんか",
      "しげき",
      "きげん"
    ],
    "correct": "しげき"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"資源\"?",
    "word": "資源",
    "options": [
      "しげん",
      "さめる",
      "せいちょう",
      "きょうふ"
    ],
    "correct": "しげん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"事件\"?",
    "word": "事件",
    "options": [
      "きんゆう",
      "へんこう",
      "じけん",
      "かける"
    ],
    "correct": "じけん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"主張\"?",
    "word": "主張",
    "options": [
      "しゅちょう",
      "ぶんせき",
      "けっか",
      "ひかく"
    ],
    "correct": "しゅちょう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"修了\"?",
    "word": "修了",
    "options": [
      "ふれる",
      "つごう",
      "こうへい",
      "しゅうりょう"
    ],
    "correct": "しゅうりょう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"種類\"?",
    "word": "種類",
    "options": [
      "しゅるい",
      "きみょう",
      "りせい",
      "ほる"
    ],
    "correct": "しゅるい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"順序\"?",
    "word": "順序",
    "options": [
      "めいれい",
      "しぜん",
      "じゅんじょ",
      "せいちょう"
    ],
    "correct": "じゅんじょ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"紹介\"?",
    "word": "紹介",
    "options": [
      "しょうかい",
      "こうへい",
      "かせぐ",
      "おしい"
    ],
    "correct": "しょうかい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"障害\"?",
    "word": "障害",
    "options": [
      "とうたつ",
      "やくわり",
      "おさえる",
      "しょうがい"
    ],
    "correct": "しょうがい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"条件\"?",
    "word": "条件",
    "options": [
      "びよう",
      "ぎょうじ",
      "めんどう",
      "じょうけん"
    ],
    "correct": "じょうけん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"商売\"?",
    "word": "商売",
    "options": [
      "つかまる",
      "ふくざつ",
      "しょうばい",
      "もくてき"
    ],
    "correct": "しょうばい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"消費\"?",
    "word": "消費",
    "options": [
      "おうさま",
      "げんきん",
      "しょうひ",
      "れいたん"
    ],
    "correct": "しょうひ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"情報\"?",
    "word": "情報",
    "options": [
      "ほうしん",
      "じょうほう",
      "にっこう",
      "こんらん"
    ],
    "correct": "じょうほう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"植物\"?",
    "word": "植物",
    "options": [
      "しめきる",
      "ひょうめん",
      "けっしん",
      "しょくぶつ"
    ],
    "correct": "しょくぶつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"処理\"?",
    "word": "処理",
    "options": [
      "ほうそう",
      "しょり",
      "きんちょう",
      "すうじ"
    ],
    "correct": "しょり"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"進歩\"?",
    "word": "進歩",
    "options": [
      "こし",
      "こくふく",
      "へんか",
      "しんぽ"
    ],
    "correct": "しんぽ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"親友\"?",
    "word": "親友",
    "options": [
      "しんゆう",
      "かさなる",
      "さいきん",
      "ちょくせつ"
    ],
    "correct": "しんゆう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"数字\"?",
    "word": "数字",
    "options": [
      "かざる",
      "しせつ",
      "ばめん",
      "すうじ"
    ],
    "correct": "すうじ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"制作\"?",
    "word": "制作",
    "options": [
      "せいさく",
      "ふこう",
      "せいじつ",
      "もくてき"
    ],
    "correct": "せいさく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"性質\"?",
    "word": "性質",
    "options": [
      "へんこう",
      "せいしつ",
      "どろ",
      "とじる"
    ],
    "correct": "せいしつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"精神\"?",
    "word": "精神",
    "options": [
      "せいしん",
      "しゅうちゅう",
      "きふ",
      "かがやく"
    ],
    "correct": "せいしん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"成長\"?",
    "word": "成長",
    "options": [
      "えんそう",
      "ぶんせき",
      "はげます",
      "せいちょう"
    ],
    "correct": "せいちょう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"誠実\"?",
    "word": "誠実",
    "options": [
      "うかがう",
      "きょういく",
      "せいじつ",
      "やくわり"
    ],
    "correct": "せいじつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"清潔\"?",
    "word": "清潔",
    "options": [
      "ひとごみ",
      "みっせつ",
      "みりょく",
      "せいけつ"
    ],
    "correct": "せいけつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"制限\"?",
    "word": "制限",
    "options": [
      "しょうじょう",
      "けっか",
      "だいひょう",
      "せいげん"
    ],
    "correct": "せいげん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"整理\"?",
    "word": "整理",
    "options": [
      "けいい",
      "てんこう",
      "てきとう",
      "せいり"
    ],
    "correct": "せいり"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"責任\"?",
    "word": "責任",
    "options": [
      "せきにん",
      "ゆか",
      "つうち",
      "ひがい"
    ],
    "correct": "せきにん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"設計\"?",
    "word": "設計",
    "options": [
      "せっけい",
      "さかり",
      "どりょく",
      "せいしん"
    ],
    "correct": "せっけい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"設備\"?",
    "word": "設備",
    "options": [
      "せつび",
      "さけぶ",
      "みごと",
      "りこん"
    ],
    "correct": "せつび"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"絶対\"?",
    "word": "絶対",
    "options": [
      "ぜったい",
      "おしい",
      "かのうせい",
      "もんく"
    ],
    "correct": "ぜったい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"宣伝\"?",
    "word": "宣伝",
    "options": [
      "うつる",
      "うで",
      "まんいん",
      "せんでん"
    ],
    "correct": "せんでん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"専門\"?",
    "word": "専門",
    "options": [
      "しやくしょ",
      "せんもん",
      "けいい",
      "がまん"
    ],
    "correct": "せんもん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"想像\"?",
    "word": "想像",
    "options": [
      "きぼう",
      "そうぞう",
      "りこん",
      "ぎょうじ"
    ],
    "correct": "そうぞう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"相談\"?",
    "word": "相談",
    "options": [
      "ふどうさん",
      "せいど",
      "そうだん",
      "ふたん"
    ],
    "correct": "そうだん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"速度\"?",
    "word": "速度",
    "options": [
      "ひょうめん",
      "そくど",
      "さかい",
      "わ"
    ],
    "correct": "そくど"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"尊敬\"?",
    "word": "尊敬",
    "options": [
      "けってい",
      "さまざま",
      "そんけい",
      "ぎゃく"
    ],
    "correct": "そんけい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"存在\"?",
    "word": "存在",
    "options": [
      "もじ",
      "おしい",
      "きょうちょう",
      "そんざい"
    ],
    "correct": "そんざい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"損害\"?",
    "word": "損害",
    "options": [
      "かさなる",
      "してん",
      "どういつ",
      "そんがい"
    ],
    "correct": "そんがい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"団体\"?",
    "word": "団体",
    "options": [
      "だんたい",
      "せいど",
      "あやしい",
      "ひひょう"
    ],
    "correct": "だんたい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"地球\"?",
    "word": "地球",
    "options": [
      "ちきゅう",
      "ほうほう",
      "かがやく",
      "じっせき"
    ],
    "correct": "ちきゅう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"知識\"?",
    "word": "知識",
    "options": [
      "さくじょ",
      "ちしき",
      "こうりゅう",
      "てきよう"
    ],
    "correct": "ちしき"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"注意\"?",
    "word": "注意",
    "options": [
      "どりょく",
      "かいけつ",
      "さっか",
      "ちゅうい"
    ],
    "correct": "ちゅうい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"調査\"?",
    "word": "調査",
    "options": [
      "しめい",
      "しょり",
      "ちょうさ",
      "ぐあい"
    ],
    "correct": "ちょうさ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"直接\"?",
    "word": "直接",
    "options": [
      "しはい",
      "かいせつ",
      "へんさい",
      "ちょくせつ"
    ],
    "correct": "ちょくせつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"通用\"?",
    "word": "通用",
    "options": [
      "そんしつ",
      "つうよう",
      "れんぞく",
      "ちいき"
    ],
    "correct": "つうよう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"都合\"?",
    "word": "都合",
    "options": [
      "しゃかい",
      "てんらんかい",
      "つごう",
      "あわてる"
    ],
    "correct": "つごう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"通知\"?",
    "word": "通知",
    "options": [
      "そくど",
      "さそう",
      "つうち",
      "てんさい"
    ],
    "correct": "つうち"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"停止\"?",
    "word": "停止",
    "options": [
      "こうこう",
      "ていし",
      "ひかく",
      "そんしつ"
    ],
    "correct": "ていし"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"適当\"?",
    "word": "適当",
    "options": [
      "ゆうせん",
      "かいせつ",
      "じょうほう",
      "てきとう"
    ],
    "correct": "てきとう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"程度\"?",
    "word": "程度",
    "options": [
      "ていど",
      "しゅうちゅう",
      "ろうどう",
      "さめる"
    ],
    "correct": "ていど"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"伝統\"?",
    "word": "伝統",
    "options": [
      "でんとう",
      "るいけい",
      "つうきん",
      "へんか"
    ],
    "correct": "でんとう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"天然\"?",
    "word": "天然",
    "options": [
      "てんねん",
      "のうりつ",
      "はげしい",
      "こんらん"
    ],
    "correct": "てんねん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"努力\"?",
    "word": "努力",
    "options": [
      "どりょく",
      "しそう",
      "せいさく",
      "せいしつ"
    ],
    "correct": "どりょく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"独特\"?",
    "word": "独特",
    "options": [
      "かよう",
      "かいけつ",
      "どくとく",
      "かわりに"
    ],
    "correct": "どくとく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"内容\"?",
    "word": "内容",
    "options": [
      "ろんぶん",
      "こうふく",
      "ないよう",
      "さそう"
    ],
    "correct": "ないよう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"悩み\"?",
    "word": "悩み",
    "options": [
      "ひがえり",
      "なやみ",
      "わく",
      "ものがたり"
    ],
    "correct": "なやみ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"日常\"?",
    "word": "日常",
    "options": [
      "にちじょう",
      "こんやく",
      "こいびと",
      "れつ"
    ],
    "correct": "にちじょう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"日光\"?",
    "word": "日光",
    "options": [
      "にっこう",
      "はっけん",
      "せんしゅ",
      "うらなう"
    ],
    "correct": "にっこう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"人数\"?",
    "word": "人数",
    "options": [
      "にんずう",
      "ちいき",
      "さいしゅう",
      "さつえい"
    ],
    "correct": "にんずう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"願う\"?",
    "word": "願う",
    "options": [
      "めいしん",
      "あくしゅ",
      "ねがう",
      "みごと"
    ],
    "correct": "ねがう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"熱中\"?",
    "word": "熱中",
    "options": [
      "ふれる",
      "ゆか",
      "はんい",
      "ねっちゅう"
    ],
    "correct": "ねっちゅう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"能率\"?",
    "word": "能率",
    "options": [
      "こうせい",
      "れいがい",
      "のうりつ",
      "さばく"
    ],
    "correct": "のうりつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"能美\"?",
    "word": "能美",
    "options": [
      "のうみ",
      "さべつ",
      "てちょう",
      "こうふく"
    ],
    "correct": "のうみ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"把握\"?",
    "word": "把握",
    "options": [
      "はあく",
      "ゆそう",
      "える",
      "うやまう"
    ],
    "correct": "はあく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"配慮\"?",
    "word": "配慮",
    "options": [
      "はいりょ",
      "れいせい",
      "けんせつ",
      "ごうかく"
    ],
    "correct": "はいりょ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"破壊\"?",
    "word": "破壊",
    "options": [
      "はかい",
      "こうせい",
      "おいこす",
      "はっけん"
    ],
    "correct": "はかい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"博士\"?",
    "word": "博士",
    "options": [
      "おいこす",
      "こううん",
      "ぎちょう",
      "はかせ"
    ],
    "correct": "はかせ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"激しい\"?",
    "word": "激しい",
    "options": [
      "げき",
      "こんざつ",
      "はげしい",
      "きゅうよ"
    ],
    "correct": "はげしい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"博物館\"?",
    "word": "博物館",
    "options": [
      "しめい",
      "はくぶつかん",
      "こし",
      "よさん"
    ],
    "correct": "はくぶつかん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"励ます\"?",
    "word": "励ます",
    "options": [
      "こんらん",
      "せんしゅ",
      "ぎょうじ",
      "はげます"
    ],
    "correct": "はげます"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"発送\"?",
    "word": "発送",
    "options": [
      "けんさ",
      "さかり",
      "はっそう",
      "しょうがくきん"
    ],
    "correct": "はっそう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"発達\"?",
    "word": "発達",
    "options": [
      "はったつ",
      "げんじつ",
      "げんきん",
      "りゅうこう"
    ],
    "correct": "はったつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"判断\"?",
    "word": "判断",
    "options": [
      "このみ",
      "しゅちょう",
      "かえる",
      "はんだん"
    ],
    "correct": "はんだん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"反対\"?",
    "word": "反対",
    "options": [
      "はんたい",
      "こうふく",
      "さまざま",
      "はんだん"
    ],
    "correct": "はんたい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"被害\"?",
    "word": "被害",
    "options": [
      "ひがい",
      "びよう",
      "のうみ",
      "ふくすう"
    ],
    "correct": "ひがい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"比較\"?",
    "word": "比較",
    "options": [
      "ひがえり",
      "ぎょうじ",
      "こてい",
      "ひかく"
    ],
    "correct": "ひかく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"非常\"?",
    "word": "非常",
    "options": [
      "ひじょう",
      "もんく",
      "ひょうばん",
      "こんざつ"
    ],
    "correct": "ひじょう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"表情\"?",
    "word": "表情",
    "options": [
      "ほぞん",
      "くみあわせ",
      "せいふ",
      "ひょうじょう"
    ],
    "correct": "ひょうじょう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"評判\"?",
    "word": "評判",
    "options": [
      "ひがえり",
      "ひょうばん",
      "はんたい",
      "かんりょう"
    ],
    "correct": "ひょうばん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"表面\"?",
    "word": "表面",
    "options": [
      "おどろかす",
      "さんこう",
      "ひょうめん",
      "つうち"
    ],
    "correct": "ひょうめん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"美容\"?",
    "word": "美容",
    "options": [
      "びよう",
      "こし",
      "おしい",
      "よゆう"
    ],
    "correct": "びよう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"負担\"?",
    "word": "負担",
    "options": [
      "ふつう",
      "ふたん",
      "うばう",
      "めいれい"
    ],
    "correct": "ふたん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"復活\"?",
    "word": "復活",
    "options": [
      "みんかん",
      "れんぞく",
      "こうへい",
      "ふっかつ"
    ],
    "correct": "ふっかつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"物質\"?",
    "word": "物質",
    "options": [
      "ぶっしつ",
      "よげん",
      "さゆう",
      "めいさく"
    ],
    "correct": "ぶっしつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"物理\"?",
    "word": "物理",
    "options": [
      "けん",
      "みつど",
      "ぶつり",
      "しげき"
    ],
    "correct": "ぶつり"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"筆記\"?",
    "word": "筆記",
    "options": [
      "しんゆう",
      "じゅんえん",
      "こんやく",
      "ひっき"
    ],
    "correct": "ひっき"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"不通\"?",
    "word": "不通",
    "options": [
      "ふつう",
      "むりょう",
      "れいせい",
      "せいげん"
    ],
    "correct": "ふつう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"不幸\"?",
    "word": "不幸",
    "options": [
      "ふこう",
      "かくじ",
      "こきゅう",
      "しぼる"
    ],
    "correct": "ふこう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"普通\"?",
    "word": "普通",
    "options": [
      "ふつう",
      "たいど",
      "もくてき",
      "ぎょうじ"
    ],
    "correct": "ふつう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"不動産\"?",
    "word": "不動産",
    "options": [
      "うで",
      "こんやく",
      "きそう",
      "ふどうさん"
    ],
    "correct": "ふどうさん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"腐敗\"?",
    "word": "腐敗",
    "options": [
      "うらやましい",
      "まるい",
      "じゅんじょ",
      "ふはい"
    ],
    "correct": "ふはい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"普及\"?",
    "word": "普及",
    "options": [
      "ふきゅう",
      "さいしょ",
      "さいのう",
      "かいせつ"
    ],
    "correct": "ふきゅう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"不足\"?",
    "word": "不足",
    "options": [
      "ふそく",
      "さす",
      "つかまる",
      "ちょきん"
    ],
    "correct": "ふそく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"分析\"?",
    "word": "分析",
    "options": [
      "ぶんせき",
      "きわめて",
      "かよう",
      "めいしょう"
    ],
    "correct": "ぶんせき"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"文章\"?",
    "word": "文章",
    "options": [
      "ひてい",
      "ししゅつ",
      "ぶんしょう",
      "しゅうかく"
    ],
    "correct": "ぶんしょう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"平均\"?",
    "word": "平均",
    "options": [
      "へいきん",
      "きねん",
      "にっこう",
      "わん"
    ],
    "correct": "へいきん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"変化\"?",
    "word": "変化",
    "options": [
      "へんか",
      "おどろかす",
      "おちつく",
      "あきる"
    ],
    "correct": "へんか"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"返事\"?",
    "word": "返事",
    "options": [
      "りこん",
      "こんらん",
      "ほぞん",
      "へんじ"
    ],
    "correct": "へんじ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"弁当\"?",
    "word": "弁当",
    "options": [
      "べんとう",
      "ひょうめん",
      "ようい",
      "ちゅうおう"
    ],
    "correct": "べんとう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"方法\"?",
    "word": "方法",
    "options": [
      "じゅんえん",
      "ふれる",
      "ほうほう",
      "さらなる"
    ],
    "correct": "ほうほう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"報告\"?",
    "word": "報告",
    "options": [
      "ほうこく",
      "れんごう",
      "せっけい",
      "きゅう"
    ],
    "correct": "ほうこく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"豊富\"?",
    "word": "豊富",
    "options": [
      "ほうふ",
      "れいぎ",
      "うったえる",
      "もくてき"
    ],
    "correct": "ほうふ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"訪問\"?",
    "word": "訪問",
    "options": [
      "かざり",
      "へんさい",
      "むすこ",
      "ほうもん"
    ],
    "correct": "ほうもん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"放送\"?",
    "word": "放送",
    "options": [
      "ほうそう",
      "すうじ",
      "せいしつ",
      "さいせい"
    ],
    "correct": "ほうそう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"法律\"?",
    "word": "法律",
    "options": [
      "えがく",
      "やとう",
      "ほぞん",
      "ほうりつ"
    ],
    "correct": "ほうりつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"微笑む\"?",
    "word": "微笑む",
    "options": [
      "ほほえむ",
      "もえる",
      "けんとう",
      "てき"
    ],
    "correct": "ほほえむ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"本格\"?",
    "word": "本格",
    "options": [
      "はんざい",
      "ざせき",
      "ほんかく",
      "りそう"
    ],
    "correct": "ほんかく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"翻訳\"?",
    "word": "翻訳",
    "options": [
      "ふしょう",
      "みごと",
      "てつ",
      "ほんやく"
    ],
    "correct": "ほんやく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"満足\"?",
    "word": "満足",
    "options": [
      "せいさく",
      "まんぞく",
      "ゆうめい",
      "じゅんじょ"
    ],
    "correct": "まんぞく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"窓口\"?",
    "word": "窓口",
    "options": [
      "ぶんせき",
      "える",
      "けっせき",
      "まどぐち"
    ],
    "correct": "まどぐち"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"丸い\"?",
    "word": "丸い",
    "options": [
      "りこう",
      "しょくぶつ",
      "まるい",
      "ひょうめん"
    ],
    "correct": "まるい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"摩擦\"?",
    "word": "摩擦",
    "options": [
      "にぎる",
      "まさつ",
      "やぶる",
      "ろうどう"
    ],
    "correct": "まさつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"未来\"?",
    "word": "未来",
    "options": [
      "ちょきん",
      "むりょう",
      "こし",
      "みらい"
    ],
    "correct": "みらい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"味方\"?",
    "word": "味方",
    "options": [
      "りょうり",
      "さいしゅう",
      "やとう",
      "みかた"
    ],
    "correct": "みかた"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"魅力\"?",
    "word": "魅力",
    "options": [
      "へんか",
      "めいわく",
      "ひてい",
      "みりょく"
    ],
    "correct": "みりょく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"名字\"?",
    "word": "名字",
    "options": [
      "さんぽ",
      "ようき",
      "てきよう",
      "みょうじ"
    ],
    "correct": "みょうじ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"民主\"?",
    "word": "民主",
    "options": [
      "こうほ",
      "かくご",
      "はっけん",
      "みんしゅ"
    ],
    "correct": "みんしゅ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"矛盾\"?",
    "word": "矛盾",
    "options": [
      "むじゅん",
      "ほうりつ",
      "さけぶ",
      "へんじ"
    ],
    "correct": "むじゅん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"無限\"?",
    "word": "無限",
    "options": [
      "むげん",
      "りゃくす",
      "けんとう",
      "えいきょう"
    ],
    "correct": "むげん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"無理\"?",
    "word": "無理",
    "options": [
      "もどる",
      "きゅう",
      "むり",
      "ていき"
    ],
    "correct": "むり"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"息子\"?",
    "word": "息子",
    "options": [
      "むすこ",
      "ていし",
      "さいてい",
      "さ"
    ],
    "correct": "むすこ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"娘\"?",
    "word": "娘",
    "options": [
      "ないよう",
      "はったつ",
      "むすめ",
      "かぎる"
    ],
    "correct": "むすめ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"名称\"?",
    "word": "名称",
    "options": [
      "かれる",
      "しゅえん",
      "おさえる",
      "めいしょう"
    ],
    "correct": "めいしょう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"迷信\"?",
    "word": "迷信",
    "options": [
      "ようき",
      "よさん",
      "しめる",
      "めいしん"
    ],
    "correct": "めいしん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"名作\"?",
    "word": "名作",
    "options": [
      "じっさい",
      "めんせき",
      "めいさく",
      "おがむ"
    ],
    "correct": "めいさく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"面積\"?",
    "word": "面積",
    "options": [
      "しやくしょ",
      "ししゅつ",
      "めんせき",
      "かかく"
    ],
    "correct": "めんせき"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"面倒\"?",
    "word": "面倒",
    "options": [
      "めんどう",
      "きょうか",
      "やくわり",
      "げけい"
    ],
    "correct": "めんどう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"申し込む\"?",
    "word": "申し込む",
    "options": [
      "はんい",
      "ふる",
      "もうしこむ",
      "ゆにゅう"
    ],
    "correct": "もうしこむ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"文字\"?",
    "word": "文字",
    "options": [
      "さいこう",
      "あくしゅ",
      "ほうもん",
      "もじ"
    ],
    "correct": "もじ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"戻る\"?",
    "word": "戻る",
    "options": [
      "しかく",
      "もどる",
      "かって",
      "びよう"
    ],
    "correct": "もどる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"物語\"?",
    "word": "物語",
    "options": [
      "しょくば",
      "ものがたり",
      "さっか",
      "りゅうがく"
    ],
    "correct": "ものがたり"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"文句\"?",
    "word": "文句",
    "options": [
      "もんく",
      "かがやく",
      "はんだん",
      "かさなる"
    ],
    "correct": "もんく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"役割\"?",
    "word": "役割",
    "options": [
      "やくわり",
      "のぞむ",
      "じっせき",
      "ぜったい"
    ],
    "correct": "やくわり"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"家賃\"?",
    "word": "家賃",
    "options": [
      "ぎょうじ",
      "れいとう",
      "めんどう",
      "やちん"
    ],
    "correct": "やちん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"厄介\"?",
    "word": "厄介",
    "options": [
      "さかい",
      "きよう",
      "やっかい",
      "みなと"
    ],
    "correct": "やっかい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"雇う\"?",
    "word": "雇う",
    "options": [
      "きほん",
      "かざり",
      "こうせい",
      "やとう"
    ],
    "correct": "やとう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"優れる\"?",
    "word": "優れる",
    "options": [
      "じょうほう",
      "ゆうしょう",
      "ひにく",
      "すぐれる"
    ],
    "correct": "すぐれる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"優勝\"?",
    "word": "優勝",
    "options": [
      "ゆうしょう",
      "ろんぶん",
      "なぐさめる",
      "ひがい"
    ],
    "correct": "ゆうしょう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"優先\"?",
    "word": "優先",
    "options": [
      "しょうがくきん",
      "へんこう",
      "きんだい",
      "ゆうせん"
    ],
    "correct": "ゆうせん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"郵便\"?",
    "word": "郵便",
    "options": [
      "ゆうびん",
      "しょうじる",
      "よそく",
      "きんちょう"
    ],
    "correct": "ゆうびん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"有利\"?",
    "word": "有利",
    "options": [
      "とし",
      "ゆうり",
      "ふどうさん",
      "つうち"
    ],
    "correct": "ゆうり"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"床\"?",
    "word": "床",
    "options": [
      "ゆか",
      "りこん",
      "しゅうかい",
      "きょうちょう"
    ],
    "correct": "ゆか"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"輸出\"?",
    "word": "輸出",
    "options": [
      "とうし",
      "こうこく",
      "ゆしゅつ",
      "かのうせい"
    ],
    "correct": "ゆしゅつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"輸入\"?",
    "word": "輸入",
    "options": [
      "ゆにゅう",
      "ゆいいつ",
      "むじゅん",
      "めんどう"
    ],
    "correct": "ゆにゅう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"譲る\"?",
    "word": "譲る",
    "options": [
      "ていき",
      "ゆずる",
      "りょかん",
      "さまざま"
    ],
    "correct": "ゆずる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"豊か\"?",
    "word": "豊か",
    "options": [
      "むじゅん",
      "ゆたか",
      "そんけい",
      "さかり"
    ],
    "correct": "ゆたか"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"許す\"?",
    "word": "許す",
    "options": [
      "かんれん",
      "きそう",
      "ゆるす",
      "にっこう"
    ],
    "correct": "ゆるす"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"余裕\"?",
    "word": "余裕",
    "options": [
      "よゆう",
      "ちしき",
      "ふくすう",
      "じしゃく"
    ],
    "correct": "よゆう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"予言\"?",
    "word": "予言",
    "options": [
      "よげん",
      "そくたつ",
      "てきよう",
      "くわしい"
    ],
    "correct": "よげん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"予測\"?",
    "word": "予測",
    "options": [
      "よそく",
      "きょか",
      "さいこう",
      "うらなう"
    ],
    "correct": "よそく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"用意\"?",
    "word": "用意",
    "options": [
      "ようい",
      "けってい",
      "せいしん",
      "ふごう"
    ],
    "correct": "ようい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"様子\"?",
    "word": "様子",
    "options": [
      "せいげん",
      "ようす",
      "しめい",
      "けっせき"
    ],
    "correct": "ようす"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"要望\"?",
    "word": "要望",
    "options": [
      "ようぼう",
      "やくわり",
      "つうち",
      "ちしき"
    ],
    "correct": "ようぼう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"陽気\"?",
    "word": "陽気",
    "options": [
      "ようき",
      "どういつ",
      "えんそう",
      "あらそう"
    ],
    "correct": "ようき"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"要素\"?",
    "word": "要素",
    "options": [
      "よくばり",
      "せいちょう",
      "ようそ",
      "ちいき"
    ],
    "correct": "ようそ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"容量\"?",
    "word": "容量",
    "options": [
      "ごうけい",
      "ゆにゅう",
      "ゆうり",
      "ようりょう"
    ],
    "correct": "ようりょう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"欲張り\"?",
    "word": "欲張り",
    "options": [
      "かなしむ",
      "おえる",
      "ほぞん",
      "よくばり"
    ],
    "correct": "よくばり"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"汚れる\"?",
    "word": "汚れる",
    "options": [
      "よごれる",
      "ごうかく",
      "ほる",
      "しんらい"
    ],
    "correct": "よごれる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"予算\"?",
    "word": "予算",
    "options": [
      "よさん",
      "はらいもどす",
      "かさなる",
      "してん"
    ],
    "correct": "よさん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"理想\"?",
    "word": "理想",
    "options": [
      "りそう",
      "ゆいいつ",
      "はら",
      "とし"
    ],
    "correct": "りそう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"理解\"?",
    "word": "理解",
    "options": [
      "きにゅう",
      "える",
      "かこ",
      "りかい"
    ],
    "correct": "りかい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"利口\"?",
    "word": "利口",
    "options": [
      "おうえん",
      "ろうどう",
      "りこう",
      "すうじ"
    ],
    "correct": "りこう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"離婚\"?",
    "word": "離婚",
    "options": [
      "りそう",
      "ひょうばん",
      "しめい",
      "りこん"
    ],
    "correct": "りこん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"率\"?",
    "word": "率",
    "options": [
      "ふれる",
      "りつ",
      "ふたん",
      "さす"
    ],
    "correct": "りつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"略す\"?",
    "word": "略す",
    "options": [
      "ぶんめい",
      "せんしゅ",
      "りゃくす",
      "きゅうよ"
    ],
    "correct": "りゃくす"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"留学\"?",
    "word": "留学",
    "options": [
      "しょうばい",
      "こじん",
      "りゅうがく",
      "うらやましい"
    ],
    "correct": "りゅうがく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"流行\"?",
    "word": "流行",
    "options": [
      "りゅうこう",
      "こうぎ",
      "ひかく",
      "のぞむ"
    ],
    "correct": "りゅうこう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"利用\"?",
    "word": "利用",
    "options": [
      "りよう",
      "してき",
      "ちいき",
      "ぜったい"
    ],
    "correct": "りよう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"料理\"?",
    "word": "料理",
    "options": [
      "きょういく",
      "ほうもん",
      "うつる",
      "りょうり"
    ],
    "correct": "りょうり"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"旅館\"?",
    "word": "旅館",
    "options": [
      "ごうかく",
      "きんにく",
      "りょかん",
      "はんだん"
    ],
    "correct": "りょかん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"冷静\"?",
    "word": "冷静",
    "options": [
      "ひとしい",
      "さっきょく",
      "かいけつ",
      "れいせい"
    ],
    "correct": "れいせい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"礼儀\"?",
    "word": "礼儀",
    "options": [
      "わき",
      "はっぴょう",
      "れいぎ",
      "かんりょう"
    ],
    "correct": "れいぎ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"冷凍\"?",
    "word": "冷凍",
    "options": [
      "かよう",
      "こし",
      "さいばん",
      "れいとう"
    ],
    "correct": "れいとう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"列\"?",
    "word": "列",
    "options": [
      "れつ",
      "きょだい",
      "えんそう",
      "しゅうかく"
    ],
    "correct": "れつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"練習\"?",
    "word": "練習",
    "options": [
      "れんしゅう",
      "さくじょ",
      "はなれる",
      "へんこう"
    ],
    "correct": "れんしゅう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"連想\"?",
    "word": "連想",
    "options": [
      "れんそう",
      "しょうひ",
      "ひがい",
      "そんざい"
    ],
    "correct": "れんそう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"連続\"?",
    "word": "連続",
    "options": [
      "れんぞく",
      "げんさん",
      "さんせい",
      "しんぽ"
    ],
    "correct": "れんぞく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"老人\"?",
    "word": "老人",
    "options": [
      "ろうじん",
      "さいこう",
      "りょうど",
      "しゅうかく"
    ],
    "correct": "ろうじん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"労働\"?",
    "word": "労働",
    "options": [
      "むじゅん",
      "さんせい",
      "ゆれる",
      "ろうどう"
    ],
    "correct": "ろうどう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"論争\"?",
    "word": "論争",
    "options": [
      "しげん",
      "やっかい",
      "せいり",
      "ろんそう"
    ],
    "correct": "ろんそう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"論文\"?",
    "word": "論文",
    "options": [
      "きゅうよう",
      "へんさい",
      "ろんぶん",
      "さけぶ"
    ],
    "correct": "ろんぶん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"輪\"?",
    "word": "輪",
    "options": [
      "わ",
      "くみたてる",
      "こんなん",
      "かざる"
    ],
    "correct": "わ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"別れ\"?",
    "word": "別れ",
    "options": [
      "さ",
      "わだい",
      "ぶっしつ",
      "わかれ"
    ],
    "correct": "わかれ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"脇\"?",
    "word": "脇",
    "options": [
      "わき",
      "かぶる",
      "おろす",
      "さ"
    ],
    "correct": "わき"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"枠\"?",
    "word": "枠",
    "options": [
      "せいげん",
      "わく",
      "ないよう",
      "はんざい"
    ],
    "correct": "わく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"わざと\"?",
    "word": "わざと",
    "options": [
      "きろく",
      "ごうか",
      "むりょう",
      "わざと"
    ],
    "correct": "わざと"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"話題\"?",
    "word": "話題",
    "options": [
      "わだい",
      "さいしゅう",
      "めいれい",
      "かなしむ"
    ],
    "correct": "わだい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"笑い\"?",
    "word": "笑い",
    "options": [
      "わらい",
      "さらなる",
      "しばふ",
      "きゅうよ"
    ],
    "correct": "わらい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"割引\"?",
    "word": "割引",
    "options": [
      "わりびき",
      "さす",
      "やくだつ",
      "はっけん"
    ],
    "correct": "わりびき"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"悪口\"?",
    "word": "悪口",
    "options": [
      "ひてい",
      "さゆう",
      "くみたてる",
      "わるくち"
    ],
    "correct": "わるくち"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"我々\"?",
    "word": "我々",
    "options": [
      "われわれ",
      "さべつ",
      "ふつう",
      "がまん"
    ],
    "correct": "われわれ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"湾\"?",
    "word": "湾",
    "options": [
      "わん",
      "かぶる",
      "さゆう",
      "わりびき"
    ],
    "correct": "わん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"腕\"?",
    "word": "腕",
    "options": [
      "こうふく",
      "うで",
      "ひょうめん",
      "てきとう"
    ],
    "correct": "うで"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"裏切る\"?",
    "word": "裏切る",
    "options": [
      "うらぎる",
      "わき",
      "じさん",
      "こえる"
    ],
    "correct": "うらぎる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"打ち消す\"?",
    "word": "打ち消す",
    "options": [
      "しげん",
      "かう",
      "うちけす",
      "はなれる"
    ],
    "correct": "うちけす"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"移る\"?",
    "word": "移る",
    "options": [
      "ひがい",
      "ふへい",
      "さかり",
      "うつる"
    ],
    "correct": "うつる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"訴える\"?",
    "word": "訴える",
    "options": [
      "うったえる",
      "ゆうめい",
      "くさい",
      "ぶつり"
    ],
    "correct": "うったえる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"奪う\"?",
    "word": "奪う",
    "options": [
      "うばう",
      "もどる",
      "あらい",
      "めいれい"
    ],
    "correct": "うばう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"敬う\"?",
    "word": "敬う",
    "options": [
      "ろうじん",
      "しはい",
      "うらなう",
      "うやまう"
    ],
    "correct": "うやまう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"占う\"?",
    "word": "占う",
    "options": [
      "はっけん",
      "だんたい",
      "ふこう",
      "うらなう"
    ],
    "correct": "うらなう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"売れる\"?",
    "word": "売れる",
    "options": [
      "うれる",
      "こたい",
      "はだ",
      "みんしゅ"
    ],
    "correct": "うれる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"描く\"?",
    "word": "描く",
    "options": [
      "ぎみ",
      "ごかい",
      "えがく",
      "とりひき"
    ],
    "correct": "えがく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"得る\"?",
    "word": "得る",
    "options": [
      "れいせい",
      "える",
      "よさん",
      "うったえる"
    ],
    "correct": "える"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"追う\"?",
    "word": "追う",
    "options": [
      "おう",
      "こうふく",
      "ほうこく",
      "ゆうしょう"
    ],
    "correct": "おう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"終える\"?",
    "word": "終える",
    "options": [
      "やっかい",
      "おうえん",
      "さかい",
      "おえる"
    ],
    "correct": "おえる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"拝む\"?",
    "word": "拝む",
    "options": [
      "よごれ",
      "おがむ",
      "さいきん",
      "そんざい"
    ],
    "correct": "おがむ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"補う\"?",
    "word": "補う",
    "options": [
      "のうぎょう",
      "おぎなう",
      "かいせつ",
      "みんかん"
    ],
    "correct": "おぎなう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"贈る\"?",
    "word": "贈る",
    "options": [
      "はいいろ",
      "てきよう",
      "ふへい",
      "おくる"
    ],
    "correct": "おくる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"怠る\"?",
    "word": "怠る",
    "options": [
      "ひかく",
      "むすめ",
      "ちゅうもく",
      "おこたる"
    ],
    "correct": "おこたる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"抑える\"?",
    "word": "抑える",
    "options": [
      "しせつ",
      "おさえる",
      "しょうかい",
      "ふどうさん"
    ],
    "correct": "おさえる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"納める\"?",
    "word": "納める",
    "options": [
      "まんぞく",
      "もんく",
      "にんずう",
      "おさめる"
    ],
    "correct": "おさめる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"恐れる\"?",
    "word": "恐れる",
    "options": [
      "しゅうりょう",
      "きゅう",
      "おそれる",
      "りこん"
    ],
    "correct": "おそれる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"教わる\"?",
    "word": "教わる",
    "options": [
      "さかい",
      "ていあん",
      "おそわる",
      "かぎる"
    ],
    "correct": "おそわる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"驚かす\"?",
    "word": "驚かす",
    "options": [
      "おどろかす",
      "せいしつ",
      "ろくおん",
      "むりょう"
    ],
    "correct": "おどろかす"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"及ぶ\"?",
    "word": "及ぶ",
    "options": [
      "こうさい",
      "およぶ",
      "くんれん",
      "してん"
    ],
    "correct": "およぶ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"織る\"?",
    "word": "織る",
    "options": [
      "じっし",
      "やっかい",
      "おる",
      "かよう"
    ],
    "correct": "おる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"折れる\"?",
    "word": "折れる",
    "options": [
      "じゅんじょ",
      "おれる",
      "かなしむ",
      "えんそう"
    ],
    "correct": "おれる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"卸す\"?",
    "word": "卸す",
    "options": [
      "おろす",
      "まどぐち",
      "ふきゅう",
      "そうさ"
    ],
    "correct": "おろす"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"返る\"?",
    "word": "返る",
    "options": [
      "かえる",
      "あわてる",
      "けしょう",
      "はんざい"
    ],
    "correct": "かえる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"替える\"?",
    "word": "替える",
    "options": [
      "かえる",
      "りつ",
      "きおん",
      "ひがい"
    ],
    "correct": "かえる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"欠ける\"?",
    "word": "欠ける",
    "options": [
      "つつむ",
      "やとう",
      "ぐんたい",
      "かける"
    ],
    "correct": "かける"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"重なる\"?",
    "word": "重なる",
    "options": [
      "まんいん",
      "くんれん",
      "かさなる",
      "ちゅうい"
    ],
    "correct": "かさなる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"飾る\"?",
    "word": "飾る",
    "options": [
      "さそう",
      "かざる",
      "ざいりょう",
      "りゅうがく"
    ],
    "correct": "かざる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"稼ぐ\"?",
    "word": "稼ぐ",
    "options": [
      "かせぐ",
      "もんく",
      "りゅうがく",
      "ぶんしょう"
    ],
    "correct": "かせぐ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"悲しむ\"?",
    "word": "悲しむ",
    "options": [
      "きょうりょく",
      "かなしむ",
      "ぎじゅつ",
      "せきにん"
    ],
    "correct": "かなしむ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"兼ねる\"?",
    "word": "兼ねる",
    "options": [
      "かねる",
      "よさん",
      "ふごう",
      "ぎょうじ"
    ],
    "correct": "かねる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"被る\"?",
    "word": "被る",
    "options": [
      "ふそく",
      "くわしい",
      "かぶる",
      "こいびと"
    ],
    "correct": "かぶる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"通う\"?",
    "word": "通う",
    "options": [
      "さんこう",
      "とうし",
      "ふくすう",
      "かよう"
    ],
    "correct": "かよう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"枯れる\"?",
    "word": "枯れる",
    "options": [
      "ほうふ",
      "はさむ",
      "さかい",
      "かれる"
    ],
    "correct": "かれる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"可愛がる\"?",
    "word": "可愛がる",
    "options": [
      "ちえ",
      "せつび",
      "かわいがる",
      "きょか"
    ],
    "correct": "かわいがる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"刻む\"?",
    "word": "刻む",
    "options": [
      "きざむ",
      "さわる",
      "きょうじゅ",
      "ぎちょう"
    ],
    "correct": "きざむ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"競う\"?",
    "word": "競う",
    "options": [
      "そんざい",
      "くいき",
      "きそう",
      "ちょきん"
    ],
    "correct": "きそう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"築く\"?",
    "word": "築く",
    "options": [
      "さめる",
      "ひにく",
      "ゆうり",
      "きずく"
    ],
    "correct": "きずく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"傷つく\"?",
    "word": "傷つく",
    "options": [
      "きずつく",
      "めいしん",
      "ふれる",
      "うやまう"
    ],
    "correct": "きずつく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"期待\"?",
    "word": "期待",
    "options": [
      "さかい",
      "きたい",
      "うやまう",
      "やくわり"
    ],
    "correct": "きたい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"貴重\"?",
    "word": "貴重",
    "options": [
      "きちょう",
      "かかえる",
      "さまざま",
      "つかまる"
    ],
    "correct": "きちょう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"議長\"?",
    "word": "議長",
    "options": [
      "わく",
      "ろうどう",
      "そんざい",
      "ぎちょう"
    ],
    "correct": "ぎちょう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"記入\"?",
    "word": "記入",
    "options": [
      "せいり",
      "りゅうこう",
      "そんがい",
      "きにゅう"
    ],
    "correct": "きにゅう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"記念\"?",
    "word": "記念",
    "options": [
      "ふたん",
      "かくだい",
      "きねん",
      "ざいさん"
    ],
    "correct": "きねん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"機能\"?",
    "word": "機能",
    "options": [
      "ほうほう",
      "せきにん",
      "ひふ",
      "きのう"
    ],
    "correct": "きのう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"希望\"?",
    "word": "希望",
    "options": [
      "びよう",
      "わるくち",
      "みりょく",
      "きぼう"
    ],
    "correct": "きぼう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"基本\"?",
    "word": "基本",
    "options": [
      "きほん",
      "もどる",
      "おぎなう",
      "はんい"
    ],
    "correct": "きほん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"決まり\"?",
    "word": "決まり",
    "options": [
      "きまり",
      "りかい",
      "ぎょうじ",
      "あらい"
    ],
    "correct": "きまり"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"奇妙\"?",
    "word": "奇妙",
    "options": [
      "はかい",
      "みらい",
      "わく",
      "きみょう"
    ],
    "correct": "きみょう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"義務\"?",
    "word": "義務",
    "options": [
      "はかせ",
      "きょういく",
      "ゆうり",
      "ぎむ"
    ],
    "correct": "ぎむ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"疑問\"?",
    "word": "疑問",
    "options": [
      "おしい",
      "こううん",
      "ゆそう",
      "ぎもん"
    ],
    "correct": "ぎもん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"逆\"?",
    "word": "逆",
    "options": [
      "ぎゃく",
      "ほうりつ",
      "ちゅうい",
      "ぎょうじ"
    ],
    "correct": "ぎゃく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"旧\"?",
    "word": "旧",
    "options": [
      "きょうふ",
      "さいしょ",
      "きゅう",
      "ちゅうおう"
    ],
    "correct": "きゅう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"級\"?",
    "word": "級",
    "options": [
      "ゆうしょう",
      "きゅう",
      "ひがえり",
      "のうみ"
    ],
    "correct": "きゅう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"給与\"?",
    "word": "給与",
    "options": [
      "きゅうよ",
      "せいしつ",
      "はんえい",
      "しゅえん"
    ],
    "correct": "きゅうよ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"急速\"?",
    "word": "急速",
    "options": [
      "へいわ",
      "ろうご",
      "くれる",
      "きゅうそく"
    ],
    "correct": "きゅうそく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"休息\"?",
    "word": "休息",
    "options": [
      "きねん",
      "せいしつ",
      "ひょうばん",
      "きゅうそく"
    ],
    "correct": "きゅうそく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"休養\"?",
    "word": "休養",
    "options": [
      "こくふく",
      "たいしょく",
      "どりょく",
      "きゅうよう"
    ],
    "correct": "きゅうよう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"清い\"?",
    "word": "清い",
    "options": [
      "めいれい",
      "きよい",
      "ふへい",
      "きょか"
    ],
    "correct": "きよい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"器用\"?",
    "word": "器用",
    "options": [
      "やぶる",
      "もくてき",
      "きよう",
      "さつ"
    ],
    "correct": "きよう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"教科\"?",
    "word": "教科",
    "options": [
      "さいじつ",
      "ぎしき",
      "きょうか",
      "ごうかく"
    ],
    "correct": "きょうか"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"境界\"?",
    "word": "境界",
    "options": [
      "ゆたか",
      "きょうかい",
      "まねく",
      "く"
    ],
    "correct": "きょうかい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"行事\"?",
    "word": "行事",
    "options": [
      "ぎょうじ",
      "すうじ",
      "ぶんめい",
      "こいびと"
    ],
    "correct": "ぎょうじ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"教授\"?",
    "word": "教授",
    "options": [
      "ふきゅう",
      "ひがい",
      "きょうつう",
      "きょうじゅ"
    ],
    "correct": "きょうじゅ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"強調\"?",
    "word": "強調",
    "options": [
      "きょうちょう",
      "げんじょう",
      "かわりに",
      "ていし"
    ],
    "correct": "きょうちょう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"共通\"?",
    "word": "共通",
    "options": [
      "よさん",
      "きょうつう",
      "りゃくす",
      "おさめる"
    ],
    "correct": "きょうつう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"協力\"?",
    "word": "協力",
    "options": [
      "はんばい",
      "からかう",
      "りよう",
      "きょうりょく"
    ],
    "correct": "きょうりょく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"極めて\"?",
    "word": "極めて",
    "options": [
      "きわめて",
      "ていしゅつ",
      "ひとこと",
      "はんにん"
    ],
    "correct": "きわめて"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"禁止\"?",
    "word": "禁止",
    "options": [
      "やちん",
      "ていし",
      "みかた",
      "きんし"
    ],
    "correct": "きんし"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"近代\"?",
    "word": "近代",
    "options": [
      "わん",
      "ようりょう",
      "きんだい",
      "さらなる"
    ],
    "correct": "きんだい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"緊張\"?",
    "word": "緊張",
    "options": [
      "もくざい",
      "きんちょう",
      "おどろかす",
      "くみたてる"
    ],
    "correct": "きんちょう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"金融\"?",
    "word": "金融",
    "options": [
      "わん",
      "きんゆう",
      "ぶんかい",
      "せいひん"
    ],
    "correct": "きんゆう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"句\"?",
    "word": "句",
    "options": [
      "く",
      "とりひき",
      "てんけい",
      "よごれ"
    ],
    "correct": "く"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"区域\"?",
    "word": "区域",
    "options": [
      "ゆうせん",
      "くいき",
      "わりびき",
      "はんい"
    ],
    "correct": "くいき"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"苦痛\"?",
    "word": "苦痛",
    "options": [
      "とうけい",
      "くつう",
      "こうこう",
      "てちょう"
    ],
    "correct": "くつう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"区別\"?",
    "word": "区別",
    "options": [
      "とらえる",
      "くべつ",
      "さいこう",
      "もくてき"
    ],
    "correct": "くべつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"組み合わせ\"?",
    "word": "組み合わせ",
    "options": [
      "くみあわせ",
      "びよう",
      "すうじ",
      "きたい"
    ],
    "correct": "くみあわせ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"組み立てる\"?",
    "word": "組み立てる",
    "options": [
      "くみたてる",
      "めいれい",
      "ひかく",
      "なぐさめる"
    ],
    "correct": "くみたてる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"訓練\"?",
    "word": "訓練",
    "options": [
      "そしき",
      "しめきる",
      "ひにく",
      "くんれん"
    ],
    "correct": "くんれん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"軍隊\"?",
    "word": "軍隊",
    "options": [
      "ぐんたい",
      "ゆうしょう",
      "むり",
      "ぎもん"
    ],
    "correct": "ぐんたい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"芸術\"?",
    "word": "芸術",
    "options": [
      "げいじゅつ",
      "むり",
      "さんせい",
      "さいてい"
    ],
    "correct": "げいじゅつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"下計\"?",
    "word": "下計",
    "options": [
      "ゆうがい",
      "さいしん",
      "ぎゃく",
      "げけい"
    ],
    "correct": "げけい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"劇\"?",
    "word": "劇",
    "options": [
      "げき",
      "けっか",
      "じゅんきゅう",
      "さいばん"
    ],
    "correct": "げき"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"欠点\"?",
    "word": "欠点",
    "options": [
      "けってん",
      "うばう",
      "きょうかい",
      "うつる"
    ],
    "correct": "けってん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"結論\"?",
    "word": "結論",
    "options": [
      "けつろん",
      "こんなん",
      "わざと",
      "かざり"
    ],
    "correct": "けつろん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"検査\"?",
    "word": "検査",
    "options": [
      "やとう",
      "けんさ",
      "さいしん",
      "のうりつ"
    ],
    "correct": "けんさ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"建設\"?",
    "word": "建設",
    "options": [
      "よそく",
      "さいしょ",
      "せいけつ",
      "けんせつ"
    ],
    "correct": "けんせつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"検討\"?",
    "word": "検討",
    "options": [
      "りそう",
      "けいい",
      "よそく",
      "けんとう"
    ],
    "correct": "けんとう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"券\"?",
    "word": "券",
    "options": [
      "へいきん",
      "りく",
      "けん",
      "ちゅうい"
    ],
    "correct": "けん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"県\"?",
    "word": "県",
    "options": [
      "けん",
      "わざと",
      "ぎょうじ",
      "けいい"
    ],
    "correct": "けん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"見解\"?",
    "word": "見解",
    "options": [
      "しやくしょ",
      "はんえい",
      "けんかい",
      "うったえる"
    ],
    "correct": "けんかい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"謙虚\"?",
    "word": "謙虚",
    "options": [
      "もんく",
      "ちゅうし",
      "はっぴょう",
      "けんきょ"
    ],
    "correct": "けんきょ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"原産\"?",
    "word": "原産",
    "options": [
      "ほうりつ",
      "げんさん",
      "そうぞう",
      "ゆそう"
    ],
    "correct": "げんさん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"現実\"?",
    "word": "現実",
    "options": [
      "げんそく",
      "はんにん",
      "たいわ",
      "げんじつ"
    ],
    "correct": "げんじつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"現象\"?",
    "word": "現象",
    "options": [
      "かわいがる",
      "けんり",
      "このみ",
      "げんしょう"
    ],
    "correct": "げんしょう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"現状\"?",
    "word": "現状",
    "options": [
      "ほんかく",
      "げんじょう",
      "ほうもん",
      "ひょうばん"
    ],
    "correct": "げんじょう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"原則\"?",
    "word": "原則",
    "options": [
      "ふつう",
      "はかい",
      "れんぞく",
      "げんそく"
    ],
    "correct": "げんそく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"現代\"?",
    "word": "現代",
    "options": [
      "げんだい",
      "りえき",
      "せんしゅ",
      "きみょう"
    ],
    "correct": "げんだい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"効果\"?",
    "word": "効果",
    "options": [
      "こうか",
      "さいのう",
      "はんざい",
      "ようい"
    ],
    "correct": "こうか"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"講義\"?",
    "word": "講義",
    "options": [
      "まよう",
      "こうぎ",
      "かいけつ",
      "きょうかしょ"
    ],
    "correct": "こうぎ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"高級\"?",
    "word": "高級",
    "options": [
      "ひきうけ",
      "きげん",
      "ゆずる",
      "こうきゅう"
    ],
    "correct": "こうきゅう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"合計\"?",
    "word": "合計",
    "options": [
      "ひてい",
      "ごうけい",
      "ふれる",
      "ぶんかい"
    ],
    "correct": "ごうけい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"構造\"?",
    "word": "構造",
    "options": [
      "さす",
      "ぎみ",
      "ふつう",
      "こうぞう"
    ],
    "correct": "こうぞう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"幸福\"?",
    "word": "幸福",
    "options": [
      "あこがれる",
      "せいのう",
      "こうふく",
      "てんじ"
    ],
    "correct": "こうふく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"公立\"?",
    "word": "公立",
    "options": [
      "やちん",
      "われわれ",
      "りこん",
      "こうりつ"
    ],
    "correct": "こうりつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"候補\"?",
    "word": "候補",
    "options": [
      "こうほ",
      "おいこす",
      "はんえい",
      "せんでん"
    ],
    "correct": "こうほ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"交流\"?",
    "word": "交流",
    "options": [
      "こうりゅう",
      "おもいで",
      "ゆか",
      "さける"
    ],
    "correct": "こうりゅう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"克服\"?",
    "word": "克服",
    "options": [
      "こくふく",
      "およぶ",
      "ていあん",
      "こううん"
    ],
    "correct": "こくふく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"腰\"?",
    "word": "腰",
    "options": [
      "こんなん",
      "はり",
      "しんぱん",
      "こし"
    ],
    "correct": "こし"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"個体\"?",
    "word": "個体",
    "options": [
      "こたい",
      "きょうつう",
      "はっぴょう",
      "たいど"
    ],
    "correct": "こたい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"固定\"?",
    "word": "固定",
    "options": [
      "みらい",
      "こてい",
      "ひてい",
      "りこん"
    ],
    "correct": "こてい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"混雑\"?",
    "word": "混雑",
    "options": [
      "かかえる",
      "こんざつ",
      "かかり",
      "りょうし"
    ],
    "correct": "こんざつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"困難\"?",
    "word": "困難",
    "options": [
      "こんらん",
      "よげん",
      "こんなん",
      "ざいさん"
    ],
    "correct": "こんなん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"婚約\"?",
    "word": "婚約",
    "options": [
      "あらそう",
      "ほしょう",
      "ひじょう",
      "こんやく"
    ],
    "correct": "こんやく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"混乱\"?",
    "word": "混乱",
    "options": [
      "こんらん",
      "くわしい",
      "ようぼう",
      "ちゅうおう"
    ],
    "correct": "こんらん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"差\"?",
    "word": "差",
    "options": [
      "みちる",
      "こうぞう",
      "しゅうかい",
      "さ"
    ],
    "correct": "さ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"際\"?",
    "word": "際",
    "options": [
      "さい",
      "ぶつり",
      "ふれる",
      "はんにん"
    ],
    "correct": "さい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"最高\"?",
    "word": "最高",
    "options": [
      "さいこう",
      "ものがたり",
      "まさつ",
      "きんにく"
    ],
    "correct": "さいこう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"財産\"?",
    "word": "財産",
    "options": [
      "ざいさん",
      "かんどう",
      "よさん",
      "ひげき"
    ],
    "correct": "ざいさん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"最終\"?",
    "word": "最終",
    "options": [
      "さいしゅう",
      "そうぞう",
      "てんさい",
      "わりびき"
    ],
    "correct": "さいしゅう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"最新\"?",
    "word": "最新",
    "options": [
      "げんしょう",
      "くみたてる",
      "ひんしつ",
      "さいしん"
    ],
    "correct": "さいしん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"才能\"?",
    "word": "才能",
    "options": [
      "さいのう",
      "やとう",
      "ちしき",
      "じゅんえん"
    ],
    "correct": "さいのう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"幸い\"?",
    "word": "幸い",
    "options": [
      "さいわい",
      "きょうじゅ",
      "のうぎょう",
      "ぶんしょう"
    ],
    "correct": "さいわい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"境\"?",
    "word": "境",
    "options": [
      "しゅうりょう",
      "さかい",
      "くさる",
      "しょり"
    ],
    "correct": "さかい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"削減\"?",
    "word": "削減",
    "options": [
      "きり",
      "さくげん",
      "がまん",
      "ちょしょ"
    ],
    "correct": "さくげん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"作成\"?",
    "word": "作成",
    "options": [
      "ていあん",
      "ようす",
      "さくせい",
      "さいぜん"
    ],
    "correct": "さくせい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"作業\"?",
    "word": "作業",
    "options": [
      "おがむ",
      "きょか",
      "さつえい",
      "さぎょう"
    ],
    "correct": "さぎょう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"削除\"?",
    "word": "削除",
    "options": [
      "ひょうめん",
      "ゆうせん",
      "りえき",
      "さくじょ"
    ],
    "correct": "さくじょ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"叫ぶ\"?",
    "word": "叫ぶ",
    "options": [
      "せきにん",
      "ゆるす",
      "さけぶ",
      "りよう"
    ],
    "correct": "さけぶ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"支える\"?",
    "word": "支える",
    "options": [
      "わかれ",
      "しょうじょう",
      "ささえる",
      "ぎちょう"
    ],
    "correct": "ささえる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"指す\"?",
    "word": "指す",
    "options": [
      "ぎちょう",
      "さす",
      "さいしょ",
      "しょくば"
    ],
    "correct": "さす"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"刺す\"?",
    "word": "刺す",
    "options": [
      "きにゅう",
      "まよう",
      "しゅうちゅう",
      "さす"
    ],
    "correct": "さす"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"座席\"?",
    "word": "座席",
    "options": [
      "めんせき",
      "こうかん",
      "そうぞう",
      "ざせき"
    ],
    "correct": "ざせき"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"誘う\"?",
    "word": "誘う",
    "options": [
      "きょか",
      "かたい",
      "はんい",
      "さそう"
    ],
    "correct": "さそう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"撮影\"?",
    "word": "撮影",
    "options": [
      "しんぱん",
      "さつえい",
      "きろく",
      "さいこう"
    ],
    "correct": "さつえい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"差別\"?",
    "word": "差別",
    "options": [
      "しょうたい",
      "さいのう",
      "ちゅうおう",
      "さべつ"
    ],
    "correct": "さべつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"様々\"?",
    "word": "様々",
    "options": [
      "かいてき",
      "にゅういん",
      "さまざま",
      "さいご"
    ],
    "correct": "さまざま"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"左右\"?",
    "word": "左右",
    "options": [
      "さゆう",
      "ざせき",
      "てんらんかい",
      "きんにく"
    ],
    "correct": "さゆう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"更なる\"?",
    "word": "更なる",
    "options": [
      "さらなる",
      "きんにく",
      "ひょうじょう",
      "きょか"
    ],
    "correct": "さらなる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"触る\"?",
    "word": "触る",
    "options": [
      "えんそう",
      "じょうほう",
      "さいしゅう",
      "さわる"
    ],
    "correct": "さわる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"参考\"?",
    "word": "参考",
    "options": [
      "くんれん",
      "りょうど",
      "さんこう",
      "きのう"
    ],
    "correct": "さんこう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"刺激\"?",
    "word": "刺激",
    "options": [
      "はんい",
      "わん",
      "ひじょう",
      "しげき"
    ],
    "correct": "しげき"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"資源\"?",
    "word": "資源",
    "options": [
      "りこん",
      "さほう",
      "しげん",
      "きょうじゅ"
    ],
    "correct": "しげん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"支持\"?",
    "word": "支持",
    "options": [
      "しじ",
      "せいしつ",
      "すぐれる",
      "せいげん"
    ],
    "correct": "しじ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"事実\"?",
    "word": "事実",
    "options": [
      "ほうもん",
      "ほうりつ",
      "ぶんけん",
      "じじつ"
    ],
    "correct": "じじつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"自然\"?",
    "word": "自然",
    "options": [
      "さべつ",
      "しめる",
      "つつむ",
      "しぜん"
    ],
    "correct": "しぜん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"持参\"?",
    "word": "持参",
    "options": [
      "やくわり",
      "しょくぎょう",
      "こううん",
      "じさん"
    ],
    "correct": "じさん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"磁石\"?",
    "word": "磁石",
    "options": [
      "たいど",
      "じしゃく",
      "へいきん",
      "ひこう"
    ],
    "correct": "じしゃく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"自身\"?",
    "word": "自身",
    "options": [
      "やくわり",
      "じしん",
      "おさえる",
      "こくふく"
    ],
    "correct": "じしん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"沈む\"?",
    "word": "沈む",
    "options": [
      "わ",
      "ちゅうもく",
      "しずむ",
      "とらえる"
    ],
    "correct": "しずむ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"思想\"?",
    "word": "思想",
    "options": [
      "へいきん",
      "はっけん",
      "しそう",
      "はたす"
    ],
    "correct": "しそう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"次第\"?",
    "word": "次第",
    "options": [
      "へんさい",
      "ひじょう",
      "しだい",
      "ふそく"
    ],
    "correct": "しだい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"施設\"?",
    "word": "施設",
    "options": [
      "しせつ",
      "きんにく",
      "かわいがる",
      "こんらん"
    ],
    "correct": "しせつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"湿気\"?",
    "word": "湿気",
    "options": [
      "しっけ",
      "ぎちょう",
      "しょうじょう",
      "きゅうそく"
    ],
    "correct": "しっけ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"実施\"?",
    "word": "実施",
    "options": [
      "さいぜん",
      "じっし",
      "はっぴょう",
      "てきよう"
    ],
    "correct": "じっし"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"実際\"?",
    "word": "実際",
    "options": [
      "じっさい",
      "こんらん",
      "わん",
      "きょうふ"
    ],
    "correct": "じっさい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"湿度\"?",
    "word": "湿度",
    "options": [
      "かぎる",
      "さっきょく",
      "しせつ",
      "しつど"
    ],
    "correct": "しつど"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"指摘\"?",
    "word": "指摘",
    "options": [
      "おがむ",
      "ふたん",
      "してき",
      "ねがう"
    ],
    "correct": "してき"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"支店\"?",
    "word": "支店",
    "options": [
      "してん",
      "もくざい",
      "しゅうせい",
      "しょうひ"
    ],
    "correct": "してん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"視点\"?",
    "word": "視点",
    "options": [
      "してん",
      "ぬく",
      "はんい",
      "じっし"
    ],
    "correct": "してん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"芝生\"?",
    "word": "芝生",
    "options": [
      "しばふ",
      "こきゅう",
      "ほほえむ",
      "おもいで"
    ],
    "correct": "しばふ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"絞る\"?",
    "word": "絞る",
    "options": [
      "もえる",
      "しばふ",
      "しぼる",
      "そしき"
    ],
    "correct": "しぼる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"司法\"?",
    "word": "司法",
    "options": [
      "しほう",
      "はたす",
      "ほうもん",
      "りゅうがく"
    ],
    "correct": "しほう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"島\"?",
    "word": "島",
    "options": [
      "つとめる",
      "きゅう",
      "はんばい",
      "しま"
    ],
    "correct": "しま"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"締め切る\"?",
    "word": "締め切る",
    "options": [
      "しはい",
      "ぬく",
      "ひかく",
      "しめきる"
    ],
    "correct": "しめきる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"湿る\"?",
    "word": "湿る",
    "options": [
      "てんらんかい",
      "こんごう",
      "しめる",
      "めんぜい"
    ],
    "correct": "しめる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"氏名\"?",
    "word": "氏名",
    "options": [
      "きょうちょう",
      "しめい",
      "ゆれる",
      "さわる"
    ],
    "correct": "しめい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"社会\"?",
    "word": "社会",
    "options": [
      "まねく",
      "ちゅうい",
      "ざいさん",
      "しゃかい"
    ],
    "correct": "しゃかい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"市役所\"?",
    "word": "市役所",
    "options": [
      "ひがい",
      "けってい",
      "めんせき",
      "しやくしょ"
    ],
    "correct": "しやくしょ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"集会\"?",
    "word": "集会",
    "options": [
      "ていあん",
      "よさん",
      "うかがう",
      "しゅうかい"
    ],
    "correct": "しゅうかい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"収穫\"?",
    "word": "収穫",
    "options": [
      "むりょう",
      "ふたん",
      "とうけい",
      "しゅうかく"
    ],
    "correct": "しゅうかく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"就職\"?",
    "word": "就職",
    "options": [
      "しゅうしょく",
      "むりょう",
      "ほる",
      "まるい"
    ],
    "correct": "しゅうしょく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"集中\"?",
    "word": "集中",
    "options": [
      "かくご",
      "はあく",
      "ぎょうじ",
      "しゅうちゅう"
    ],
    "correct": "しゅうちゅう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"住民\"?",
    "word": "住民",
    "options": [
      "わく",
      "じゅうみん",
      "けいき",
      "どうとく"
    ],
    "correct": "じゅうみん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"終了\"?",
    "word": "終了",
    "options": [
      "こうしょう",
      "しゅうりょう",
      "はらいもどす",
      "けいえい"
    ],
    "correct": "しゅうりょう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"主演\"?",
    "word": "主演",
    "options": [
      "しめい",
      "ぶんめい",
      "きゅうよ",
      "しゅえん"
    ],
    "correct": "しゅえん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"守備\"?",
    "word": "守備",
    "options": [
      "みんしゅ",
      "しょうにん",
      "ふそく",
      "しゅび"
    ],
    "correct": "しゅび"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"順延\"?",
    "word": "順延",
    "options": [
      "めいれい",
      "わん",
      "やちん",
      "じゅんえん"
    ],
    "correct": "じゅんえん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"準急\"?",
    "word": "準急",
    "options": [
      "じゅんきゅう",
      "じしん",
      "きょうつう",
      "しょくぎょう"
    ],
    "correct": "じゅんきゅう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"順序\"?",
    "word": "順序",
    "options": [
      "しめきる",
      "さそう",
      "じゅんじょ",
      "こし"
    ],
    "correct": "じゅんじょ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"症状\"?",
    "word": "症状",
    "options": [
      "きんちょう",
      "しょうじょう",
      "ごうかく",
      "やっかい"
    ],
    "correct": "しょうじょう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"生じる\"?",
    "word": "生じる",
    "options": [
      "ほうそう",
      "ゆそう",
      "しょうじる",
      "ろんぶん"
    ],
    "correct": "しょうじる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"招待\"?",
    "word": "招待",
    "options": [
      "けつろん",
      "くつう",
      "うやまう",
      "しょうたい"
    ],
    "correct": "しょうたい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"承認\"?",
    "word": "承認",
    "options": [
      "かかり",
      "ざせき",
      "れんぞく",
      "しょうにん"
    ],
    "correct": "しょうにん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"証明\"?",
    "word": "証明",
    "options": [
      "じゅうみん",
      "しょうめい",
      "きんにく",
      "かいぜん"
    ],
    "correct": "しょうめい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"奨学金\"?",
    "word": "奨学金",
    "options": [
      "かいぜん",
      "しょうがくきん",
      "どうさ",
      "ゆうびん"
    ],
    "correct": "しょうがくきん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"商売\"?",
    "word": "商売",
    "options": [
      "しょうばい",
      "むすこ",
      "せきにん",
      "きみょう"
    ],
    "correct": "しょうばい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"消費\"?",
    "word": "消費",
    "options": [
      "ひこう",
      "ぶんけん",
      "はっこう",
      "しょうひ"
    ],
    "correct": "しょうひ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"製品\"?",
    "word": "製品",
    "options": [
      "ととのう",
      "ひがい",
      "りえき",
      "せいひん"
    ],
    "correct": "せいひん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"政府\"?",
    "word": "政府",
    "options": [
      "ないよう",
      "りそう",
      "ていあん",
      "せいふ"
    ],
    "correct": "せいふ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"整理\"?",
    "word": "整理",
    "options": [
      "めぐまれる",
      "さす",
      "そしき",
      "せいり"
    ],
    "correct": "せいり"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"責任\"?",
    "word": "責任",
    "options": [
      "せきにん",
      "きり",
      "じゅんえん",
      "きょうりょく"
    ],
    "correct": "せきにん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"選挙\"?",
    "word": "選挙",
    "options": [
      "てってい",
      "ゆれる",
      "かんり",
      "せんきょ"
    ],
    "correct": "せんきょ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"選手\"?",
    "word": "選手",
    "options": [
      "せんしゅ",
      "つねに",
      "ひにく",
      "はんにん"
    ],
    "correct": "せんしゅ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"相当\"?",
    "word": "相当",
    "options": [
      "おろす",
      "とし",
      "こうきゅう",
      "そうとう"
    ],
    "correct": "そうとう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"操作\"?",
    "word": "操作",
    "options": [
      "そうさ",
      "けんかい",
      "きょだい",
      "ろんそう"
    ],
    "correct": "そうさ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"速達\"?",
    "word": "速達",
    "options": [
      "ぶんけん",
      "ていしゅつ",
      "そくたつ",
      "りこん"
    ],
    "correct": "そくたつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"測定\"?",
    "word": "測定",
    "options": [
      "だんたい",
      "はくぶつかん",
      "こんらん",
      "そくてい"
    ],
    "correct": "そくてい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"組織\"?",
    "word": "組織",
    "options": [
      "わん",
      "そしき",
      "やっかい",
      "しずむ"
    ],
    "correct": "そしき"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"損失\"?",
    "word": "損失",
    "options": [
      "そんしつ",
      "さいこう",
      "しんぽ",
      "かいぜん"
    ],
    "correct": "そんしつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"態度\"?",
    "word": "態度",
    "options": [
      "きおく",
      "じゅうみん",
      "たいど",
      "さいきん"
    ],
    "correct": "たいど"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"体験\"?",
    "word": "体験",
    "options": [
      "こいびと",
      "さいこう",
      "せつび",
      "たいけん"
    ],
    "correct": "たいけん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"対話\"?",
    "word": "対話",
    "options": [
      "たいわ",
      "きょうかしょ",
      "おこたる",
      "やっかい"
    ],
    "correct": "たいわ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"蓄える\"?",
    "word": "蓄える",
    "options": [
      "こんざつ",
      "たくわえる",
      "しゃかい",
      "ゆうり"
    ],
    "correct": "たくわえる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"担当\"?",
    "word": "担当",
    "options": [
      "みょうじ",
      "うちけす",
      "おそろしい",
      "たんとう"
    ],
    "correct": "たんとう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"地域\"?",
    "word": "地域",
    "options": [
      "ちいき",
      "りかい",
      "りゅうがく",
      "きふ"
    ],
    "correct": "ちいき"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"知恵\"?",
    "word": "知恵",
    "options": [
      "さくじょ",
      "ふくめる",
      "はあく",
      "ちえ"
    ],
    "correct": "ちえ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"遅刻\"?",
    "word": "遅刻",
    "options": [
      "せんきょ",
      "さめる",
      "ちこく",
      "ほうりつ"
    ],
    "correct": "ちこく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"知識\"?",
    "word": "知識",
    "options": [
      "しゅうしょく",
      "せいしん",
      "きんちょう",
      "ちしき"
    ],
    "correct": "ちしき"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"秩序\"?",
    "word": "秩序",
    "options": [
      "ちつじょ",
      "おいこす",
      "しょうがい",
      "ようりょう"
    ],
    "correct": "ちつじょ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"抽選\"?",
    "word": "抽選",
    "options": [
      "げんじつ",
      "けっか",
      "ちゅうせん",
      "にちじょう"
    ],
    "correct": "ちゅうせん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"注目\"?",
    "word": "注目",
    "options": [
      "しだい",
      "ちゅうもく",
      "れいとう",
      "かう"
    ],
    "correct": "ちゅうもく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"貯金\"?",
    "word": "貯金",
    "options": [
      "ちょきん",
      "だいひょう",
      "ざいさん",
      "こんらん"
    ],
    "correct": "ちょきん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"著書\"?",
    "word": "著書",
    "options": [
      "ふしょう",
      "ちょしょ",
      "けっか",
      "はげしい"
    ],
    "correct": "ちょしょ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"追加\"?",
    "word": "追加",
    "options": [
      "わざと",
      "ついか",
      "かなしむ",
      "えんりょ"
    ],
    "correct": "ついか"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"通貨\"?",
    "word": "通貨",
    "options": [
      "しめい",
      "たいしょく",
      "わだい",
      "つうか"
    ],
    "correct": "つうか"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"通勤\"?",
    "word": "通勤",
    "options": [
      "ゆうせん",
      "つうきん",
      "なぐさめる",
      "はいふ"
    ],
    "correct": "つうきん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"通知\"?",
    "word": "通知",
    "options": [
      "かくご",
      "とじる",
      "つうち",
      "まんぞく"
    ],
    "correct": "つうち"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"捕まる\"?",
    "word": "捕まる",
    "options": [
      "ひょうじょう",
      "しょうじる",
      "こくふく",
      "つかまる"
    ],
    "correct": "つかまる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"包む\"?",
    "word": "包む",
    "options": [
      "じっし",
      "せつび",
      "かいふく",
      "つつむ"
    ],
    "correct": "つつむ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"勤める\"?",
    "word": "勤める",
    "options": [
      "けいい",
      "こうさい",
      "ちえ",
      "つとめる"
    ],
    "correct": "つとめる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"繋ぐ\"?",
    "word": "繋ぐ",
    "options": [
      "つなぐ",
      "はらいもどす",
      "ろんぶん",
      "かざり"
    ],
    "correct": "つなぐ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"常に\"?",
    "word": "常に",
    "options": [
      "ぎしき",
      "ひてい",
      "つうち",
      "つねに"
    ],
    "correct": "つねに"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"提案\"?",
    "word": "提案",
    "options": [
      "かかえる",
      "ないよう",
      "しゅうしょく",
      "ていあん"
    ],
    "correct": "ていあん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"定期\"?",
    "word": "定期",
    "options": [
      "めいさく",
      "ていき",
      "くべつ",
      "うちけす"
    ],
    "correct": "ていき"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"提出\"?",
    "word": "提出",
    "options": [
      "ふくらむ",
      "ていしゅつ",
      "こうりゅう",
      "ぎむ"
    ],
    "correct": "ていしゅつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"敵\"?",
    "word": "敵",
    "options": [
      "てき",
      "ぎょうじ",
      "かえる",
      "とざん"
    ],
    "correct": "てき"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"適当\"?",
    "word": "適当",
    "options": [
      "こんらん",
      "きざむ",
      "はかせ",
      "てきとう"
    ],
    "correct": "てきとう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"適用\"?",
    "word": "適用",
    "options": [
      "てきよう",
      "はかせ",
      "きょか",
      "ゆうせん"
    ],
    "correct": "てきよう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"鉄\"?",
    "word": "鉄",
    "options": [
      "てつ",
      "さくせい",
      "わざと",
      "れつ"
    ],
    "correct": "てつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"徹底\"?",
    "word": "徹底",
    "options": [
      "きかい",
      "さいしん",
      "てってい",
      "せつび"
    ],
    "correct": "てってい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"手帳\"?",
    "word": "手帳",
    "options": [
      "てちょう",
      "しめい",
      "こうこう",
      "やちん"
    ],
    "correct": "てちょう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"添加\"?",
    "word": "添加",
    "options": [
      "てんか",
      "ほけん",
      "きたい",
      "てきとう"
    ],
    "correct": "てんか"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"典型\"?",
    "word": "典型",
    "options": [
      "ていあん",
      "てんけい",
      "こんやく",
      "たいけん"
    ],
    "correct": "てんけい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"展示\"?",
    "word": "展示",
    "options": [
      "はく",
      "こくさい",
      "きぼう",
      "てんじ"
    ],
    "correct": "てんじ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"天候\"?",
    "word": "天候",
    "options": [
      "りゃくす",
      "はいいろ",
      "てんこう",
      "びよう"
    ],
    "correct": "てんこう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"天才\"?",
    "word": "天才",
    "options": [
      "うらやましい",
      "ふか",
      "てんらんかい",
      "てんさい"
    ],
    "correct": "てんさい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"検討\"?",
    "word": "検討",
    "options": [
      "きゅう",
      "さんか",
      "けってん",
      "けんとう"
    ],
    "correct": "けんとう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"同一\"?",
    "word": "同一",
    "options": [
      "きおん",
      "もじ",
      "ゆうせん",
      "どういつ"
    ],
    "correct": "どういつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"統計\"?",
    "word": "統計",
    "options": [
      "とうけい",
      "けんり",
      "しはい",
      "けしき"
    ],
    "correct": "とうけい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"動作\"?",
    "word": "動作",
    "options": [
      "ていあん",
      "どうさ",
      "そうだん",
      "こくさい"
    ],
    "correct": "どうさ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"到達\"?",
    "word": "到達",
    "options": [
      "ことば",
      "がまん",
      "とうたつ",
      "まさつ"
    ],
    "correct": "とうたつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"道徳\"?",
    "word": "道徳",
    "options": [
      "めんぜい",
      "きらう",
      "どうとく",
      "へんじ"
    ],
    "correct": "どうとく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"透明\"?",
    "word": "透明",
    "options": [
      "じゅんきゅう",
      "さいのう",
      "ひかく",
      "とうめい"
    ],
    "correct": "とうめい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"独特\"?",
    "word": "独特",
    "options": [
      "こんやく",
      "かんり",
      "どくとく",
      "のぞむ"
    ],
    "correct": "どくとく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"独立\"?",
    "word": "独立",
    "options": [
      "けっせき",
      "どくりつ",
      "ゆしゅつ",
      "おもいで"
    ],
    "correct": "どくりつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"登山\"?",
    "word": "登山",
    "options": [
      "ぶんせき",
      "おそろしい",
      "ごかい",
      "とざん"
    ],
    "correct": "とざん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"都市\"?",
    "word": "都市",
    "options": [
      "とし",
      "やくわり",
      "ゆうめい",
      "はんたい"
    ],
    "correct": "とし"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"閉じる\"?",
    "word": "閉じる",
    "options": [
      "とじる",
      "にっき",
      "めんせき",
      "あつかましい"
    ],
    "correct": "とじる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"届ける\"?",
    "word": "届ける",
    "options": [
      "しょうがくきん",
      "わるくち",
      "こうほ",
      "とどける"
    ],
    "correct": "とどける"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"整う\"?",
    "word": "整う",
    "options": [
      "ととのう",
      "てきとう",
      "みっせつ",
      "そしき"
    ],
    "correct": "ととのう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"泊まる\"?",
    "word": "泊まる",
    "options": [
      "とらえる",
      "とまる",
      "ごうかく",
      "やとう"
    ],
    "correct": "とまる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"富む\"?",
    "word": "富む",
    "options": [
      "とむ",
      "りょかん",
      "かわいがる",
      "かのうせい"
    ],
    "correct": "とむ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"捕らえる\"?",
    "word": "捕らえる",
    "options": [
      "とらえる",
      "ほうもん",
      "ささえる",
      "うちけす"
    ],
    "correct": "とらえる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"取引\"?",
    "word": "取引",
    "options": [
      "きんゆう",
      "てんさい",
      "とりひき",
      "やくわり"
    ],
    "correct": "とりひき"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"努力\"?",
    "word": "努力",
    "options": [
      "どりょく",
      "へんしゅう",
      "ひょうめん",
      "ちゅうい"
    ],
    "correct": "どりょく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"泥\"?",
    "word": "泥",
    "options": [
      "どろ",
      "さかい",
      "たいど",
      "ちゅうし"
    ],
    "correct": "どろ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"握る\"?",
    "word": "握る",
    "options": [
      "はなれる",
      "にぎる",
      "さいこう",
      "たんとう"
    ],
    "correct": "にぎる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"虹\"?",
    "word": "虹",
    "options": [
      "にじ",
      "さつえい",
      "ししゅつ",
      "のうりつ"
    ],
    "correct": "にじ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"日記\"?",
    "word": "日記",
    "options": [
      "ゆそう",
      "だいひょう",
      "にっき",
      "ひかく"
    ],
    "correct": "にっき"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"入院\"?",
    "word": "入院",
    "options": [
      "しゅうかい",
      "みちびく",
      "にゅういん",
      "きり"
    ],
    "correct": "にゅういん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"人間\"?",
    "word": "人間",
    "options": [
      "ないよう",
      "にんげん",
      "きょうつう",
      "こうこく"
    ],
    "correct": "にんげん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"抜く\"?",
    "word": "抜く",
    "options": [
      "ぬく",
      "しょうたい",
      "さ",
      "さいしゅう"
    ],
    "correct": "ぬく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"布\"?",
    "word": "布",
    "options": [
      "ふたん",
      "ぬの",
      "まるい",
      "ていしゅつ"
    ],
    "correct": "ぬの"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"願う\"?",
    "word": "願う",
    "options": [
      "きんちょう",
      "むすこ",
      "よげん",
      "ねがう"
    ],
    "correct": "ねがう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"及ぶ\"?",
    "word": "及ぶ",
    "options": [
      "けいき",
      "ほうもん",
      "およぶ",
      "こくふく"
    ],
    "correct": "およぶ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"望む\"?",
    "word": "望む",
    "options": [
      "ゆうせん",
      "せいひん",
      "のぞむ",
      "さす"
    ],
    "correct": "のぞむ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"伸ばす\"?",
    "word": "伸ばす",
    "options": [
      "のばす",
      "ほうそう",
      "そうだん",
      "ひょうめん"
    ],
    "correct": "のばす"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"上る\"?",
    "word": "上る",
    "options": [
      "のぼる",
      "しょくぎょう",
      "こうふく",
      "とどける"
    ],
    "correct": "のぼる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"灰色\"?",
    "word": "灰色",
    "options": [
      "おしい",
      "かかえる",
      "はいいろ",
      "さけぶ"
    ],
    "correct": "はいいろ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"配布\"?",
    "word": "配布",
    "options": [
      "じゅんえん",
      "ははおや",
      "はいふ",
      "こうぞう"
    ],
    "correct": "はいふ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"激しい\"?",
    "word": "激しい",
    "options": [
      "てんじ",
      "はげしい",
      "やちん",
      "とうめい"
    ],
    "correct": "はげしい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"図る\"?",
    "word": "図る",
    "options": [
      "はかる",
      "しゃかい",
      "ひひょう",
      "てんか"
    ],
    "correct": "はかる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"吐く\"?",
    "word": "吐く",
    "options": [
      "じき",
      "せっけい",
      "けってい",
      "はく"
    ],
    "correct": "はく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"爆発\"?",
    "word": "爆発",
    "options": [
      "ばくはつ",
      "うらぎる",
      "かたい",
      "くろう"
    ],
    "correct": "ばくはつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"挟む\"?",
    "word": "挟む",
    "options": [
      "はさむ",
      "おしい",
      "みょうじ",
      "しめる"
    ],
    "correct": "はさむ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"果たす\"?",
    "word": "果たす",
    "options": [
      "はたす",
      "ひとしい",
      "ぎょうじ",
      "そうとう"
    ],
    "correct": "はたす"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"肌\"?",
    "word": "肌",
    "options": [
      "はだ",
      "やとう",
      "わりびき",
      "けっかん"
    ],
    "correct": "はだ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"働く\"?",
    "word": "働く",
    "options": [
      "はたらく",
      "ささえる",
      "しょうかい",
      "うれる"
    ],
    "correct": "はたらく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"発見\"?",
    "word": "発見",
    "options": [
      "こし",
      "どうさ",
      "かぎる",
      "はっけん"
    ],
    "correct": "はっけん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"発行\"?",
    "word": "発行",
    "options": [
      "このみ",
      "さんか",
      "きんちょう",
      "はっこう"
    ],
    "correct": "はっこう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"発生\"?",
    "word": "発生",
    "options": [
      "さぎょう",
      "とし",
      "はっせい",
      "さす"
    ],
    "correct": "はっせい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"発表\"?",
    "word": "発表",
    "options": [
      "はっぴょう",
      "きんにく",
      "さいのう",
      "けってい"
    ],
    "correct": "はっぴょう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"発明\"?",
    "word": "発明",
    "options": [
      "ひっき",
      "ちょきん",
      "さいぜん",
      "はつめい"
    ],
    "correct": "はつめい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"放れる\"?",
    "word": "放れる",
    "options": [
      "かくにん",
      "とうたつ",
      "ぜったい",
      "はなれる"
    ],
    "correct": "はなれる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"幅\"?",
    "word": "幅",
    "options": [
      "はば",
      "つうち",
      "てんらんかい",
      "かいせつ"
    ],
    "correct": "はば"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"母親\"?",
    "word": "母親",
    "options": [
      "ははおや",
      "さっきょく",
      "げんじょう",
      "はいふ"
    ],
    "correct": "ははおや"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"場面\"?",
    "word": "場面",
    "options": [
      "しげん",
      "けっしん",
      "けんこう",
      "ばめん"
    ],
    "correct": "ばめん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"腹\"?",
    "word": "腹",
    "options": [
      "よろこび",
      "はら",
      "つなぐ",
      "けんそん"
    ],
    "correct": "はら"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"払い戻す\"?",
    "word": "払い戻す",
    "options": [
      "りゅうがく",
      "ふきん",
      "ていあん",
      "はらいもどす"
    ],
    "correct": "はらいもどす"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"針\"?",
    "word": "針",
    "options": [
      "ごうかく",
      "さんせい",
      "ふる",
      "はり"
    ],
    "correct": "はり"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"範囲\"?",
    "word": "範囲",
    "options": [
      "はんい",
      "そしき",
      "さす",
      "かう"
    ],
    "correct": "はんい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"反映\"?",
    "word": "反映",
    "options": [
      "せきにん",
      "そうとう",
      "はんえい",
      "ばめん"
    ],
    "correct": "はんえい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"判断\"?",
    "word": "判断",
    "options": [
      "はんだん",
      "うちけす",
      "どりょく",
      "こううん"
    ],
    "correct": "はんだん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"犯人\"?",
    "word": "犯人",
    "options": [
      "つうよう",
      "りよう",
      "こくふく",
      "はんにん"
    ],
    "correct": "はんにん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"販売\"?",
    "word": "販売",
    "options": [
      "はんばい",
      "さけぶ",
      "とうし",
      "ふはい"
    ],
    "correct": "はんばい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"比較\"?",
    "word": "比較",
    "options": [
      "けってん",
      "ようそ",
      "こんざつ",
      "ひかく"
    ],
    "correct": "ひかく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"日帰り\"?",
    "word": "日帰り",
    "options": [
      "きそう",
      "くみあわせ",
      "つとめる",
      "ひがえり"
    ],
    "correct": "ひがえり"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"非行\"?",
    "word": "非行",
    "options": [
      "わりびき",
      "ひこう",
      "ふくざつ",
      "くわしい"
    ],
    "correct": "ひこう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"被害\"?",
    "word": "被害",
    "options": [
      "さいぜん",
      "こんざつ",
      "つうよう",
      "ひがい"
    ],
    "correct": "ひがい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"引受\"?",
    "word": "引受",
    "options": [
      "はなれる",
      "うやまう",
      "ひがい",
      "ひきうけ"
    ],
    "correct": "ひきうけ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"悲劇\"?",
    "word": "悲劇",
    "options": [
      "ひげき",
      "くんれん",
      "かみがた",
      "けいき"
    ],
    "correct": "ひげき"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"飛行\"?",
    "word": "飛行",
    "options": [
      "ひこう",
      "ざいさん",
      "じゅんじょ",
      "げき"
    ],
    "correct": "ひこう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"非常\"?",
    "word": "非常",
    "options": [
      "きょうか",
      "しゃかい",
      "さめる",
      "ひじょう"
    ],
    "correct": "ひじょう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"必需品\"?",
    "word": "必需品",
    "options": [
      "ひつじゅひん",
      "さす",
      "こうぎ",
      "きょだい"
    ],
    "correct": "ひつじゅひん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"否定\"?",
    "word": "否定",
    "options": [
      "ひょうめん",
      "ひてい",
      "ふきゅう",
      "めいしん"
    ],
    "correct": "ひてい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"一言\"?",
    "word": "一言",
    "options": [
      "ひとこと",
      "こてい",
      "かわいがる",
      "はつめい"
    ],
    "correct": "ひとこと"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"人込み\"?",
    "word": "人込み",
    "options": [
      "えがく",
      "ひとごみ",
      "へんか",
      "さそう"
    ],
    "correct": "ひとごみ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"等しい\"?",
    "word": "等しい",
    "options": [
      "りこん",
      "みらい",
      "ひとしい",
      "ささえる"
    ],
    "correct": "ひとしい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"一人称\"?",
    "word": "一人称",
    "options": [
      "いちにんしょう",
      "めいかく",
      "みらい",
      "きふ"
    ],
    "correct": "いちにんしょう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"皮肉\"?",
    "word": "皮肉",
    "options": [
      "ひにく",
      "さいのう",
      "けっか",
      "りそう"
    ],
    "correct": "ひにく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"皮膚\"?",
    "word": "皮膚",
    "options": [
      "ひふ",
      "きゅうよう",
      "そうぞう",
      "せんでん"
    ],
    "correct": "ひふ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"批評\"?",
    "word": "批評",
    "options": [
      "たいけん",
      "ほうそく",
      "ひひょう",
      "とうめい"
    ],
    "correct": "ひひょう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"表面\"?",
    "word": "表面",
    "options": [
      "けんめい",
      "ひょうめん",
      "つごう",
      "けんとう"
    ],
    "correct": "ひょうめん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"評判\"?",
    "word": "評判",
    "options": [
      "ふつう",
      "ちょくせつ",
      "れんそう",
      "ひょうばん"
    ],
    "correct": "ひょうばん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"品質\"?",
    "word": "品質",
    "options": [
      "しせつ",
      "ひんしつ",
      "こてい",
      "ゆうれい"
    ],
    "correct": "ひんしつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"貧乏\"?",
    "word": "貧乏",
    "options": [
      "びんぼう",
      "ひげき",
      "かんれん",
      "せいけつ"
    ],
    "correct": "びんぼう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"不可\"?",
    "word": "不可",
    "options": [
      "ふか",
      "ぶんめい",
      "けんきょ",
      "うちけす"
    ],
    "correct": "ふか"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"武器\"?",
    "word": "武器",
    "options": [
      "そうさ",
      "きふ",
      "ぶき",
      "とし"
    ],
    "correct": "ぶき"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"復習\"?",
    "word": "復習",
    "options": [
      "ふくしゅう",
      "ゆたか",
      "ひこう",
      "さくせい"
    ],
    "correct": "ふくしゅう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"複雑\"?",
    "word": "複雑",
    "options": [
      "ふくざつ",
      "ものがたり",
      "こんらん",
      "ぎちょう"
    ],
    "correct": "ふくざつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"複数\"?",
    "word": "複数",
    "options": [
      "わるくち",
      "ふくすう",
      "おる",
      "ひがえり"
    ],
    "correct": "ふくすう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"含める\"?",
    "word": "含める",
    "options": [
      "ふくめる",
      "さいこう",
      "てきとう",
      "とじる"
    ],
    "correct": "ふくめる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"膨らむ\"?",
    "word": "膨らむ",
    "options": [
      "ふくらむ",
      "せいさく",
      "はんい",
      "そんけい"
    ],
    "correct": "ふくらむ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"普及\"?",
    "word": "普及",
    "options": [
      "よゆう",
      "くべつ",
      "ゆしゅつ",
      "ふきゅう"
    ],
    "correct": "ふきゅう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"符号\"?",
    "word": "符号",
    "options": [
      "ふごう",
      "かくじ",
      "せんしゅ",
      "かくだい"
    ],
    "correct": "ふごう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"負傷\"?",
    "word": "負傷",
    "options": [
      "ざいりょう",
      "ほうほう",
      "げんしょう",
      "ふしょう"
    ],
    "correct": "ふしょう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"舞台\"?",
    "word": "舞台",
    "options": [
      "かたい",
      "ふきゅう",
      "たいど",
      "ぶたい"
    ],
    "correct": "ぶたい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"負担\"?",
    "word": "負担",
    "options": [
      "ふたん",
      "くれる",
      "われわれ",
      "ろくおん"
    ],
    "correct": "ふたん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"付近\"?",
    "word": "付近",
    "options": [
      "せいげん",
      "はんい",
      "きょうかい",
      "ふきん"
    ],
    "correct": "ふきん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"不平\"?",
    "word": "不平",
    "options": [
      "けんとう",
      "おう",
      "ふへい",
      "かよう"
    ],
    "correct": "ふへい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"不用\"?",
    "word": "不用",
    "options": [
      "わん",
      "けっしん",
      "ふよう",
      "ざいりょう"
    ],
    "correct": "ふよう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"不運\"?",
    "word": "不運",
    "options": [
      "せいしん",
      "めいかく",
      "ふうん",
      "りせい"
    ],
    "correct": "ふうん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"不通\"?",
    "word": "不通",
    "options": [
      "ふつう",
      "とうたつ",
      "ぎもん",
      "うちけす"
    ],
    "correct": "ふつう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"振る\"?",
    "word": "振る",
    "options": [
      "かさなる",
      "もちあげる",
      "むせん",
      "ふる"
    ],
    "correct": "ふる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"触れる\"?",
    "word": "触れる",
    "options": [
      "ふれる",
      "よそく",
      "さいきん",
      "もどる"
    ],
    "correct": "ふれる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"分析\"?",
    "word": "分析",
    "options": [
      "こうこく",
      "わざと",
      "ぶんせき",
      "かいせい"
    ],
    "correct": "ぶんせき"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"分解\"?",
    "word": "分解",
    "options": [
      "しゃかい",
      "さいせい",
      "みょうじ",
      "ぶんかい"
    ],
    "correct": "ぶんかい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"文献\"?",
    "word": "文献",
    "options": [
      "りこん",
      "ぶんめい",
      "はんたい",
      "ぶんけん"
    ],
    "correct": "ぶんけん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"文明\"?",
    "word": "文明",
    "options": [
      "ささえる",
      "はんだん",
      "ぶんめい",
      "かくご"
    ],
    "correct": "ぶんめい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"平均\"?",
    "word": "平均",
    "options": [
      "きたい",
      "こうむいん",
      "へいきん",
      "れんしゅう"
    ],
    "correct": "へいきん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"平和\"?",
    "word": "平和",
    "options": [
      "りかい",
      "はかる",
      "ふきゅう",
      "へいわ"
    ],
    "correct": "へいわ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"変化\"?",
    "word": "変化",
    "options": [
      "へんか",
      "じじょう",
      "こくさい",
      "ぎじゅつ"
    ],
    "correct": "へんか"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"変更\"?",
    "word": "変更",
    "options": [
      "せいしん",
      "まねく",
      "かくご",
      "へんこう"
    ],
    "correct": "へんこう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"返済\"?",
    "word": "返済",
    "options": [
      "へんさい",
      "しゃかい",
      "かいせつ",
      "さばく"
    ],
    "correct": "へんさい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"編集\"?",
    "word": "編集",
    "options": [
      "ちいき",
      "へんしゅう",
      "さけぶ",
      "かいせい"
    ],
    "correct": "へんしゅう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"便利\"?",
    "word": "便利",
    "options": [
      "めんせき",
      "つねに",
      "さべつ",
      "べんり"
    ],
    "correct": "べんり"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"暮れる\"?",
    "word": "暮れる",
    "options": [
      "ほうそう",
      "かぎる",
      "にぎる",
      "くれる"
    ],
    "correct": "くれる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"法則\"?",
    "word": "法則",
    "options": [
      "ふくめる",
      "せんでん",
      "りそう",
      "ほうそく"
    ],
    "correct": "ほうそく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"方針\"?",
    "word": "方針",
    "options": [
      "ぎょうじ",
      "のうぎょう",
      "ひょうばん",
      "ほうしん"
    ],
    "correct": "ほうしん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"放送\"?",
    "word": "放送",
    "options": [
      "ほうそう",
      "そんけい",
      "のうりつ",
      "げんかい"
    ],
    "correct": "ほうそう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"豊富\"?",
    "word": "豊富",
    "options": [
      "ほうふ",
      "ようす",
      "とうけい",
      "きゅうよ"
    ],
    "correct": "ほうふ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"方法\"?",
    "word": "方法",
    "options": [
      "きおく",
      "ほうほう",
      "じゅんじょ",
      "かいぜん"
    ],
    "correct": "ほうほう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"訪問\"?",
    "word": "訪問",
    "options": [
      "ほうもん",
      "かいせつ",
      "よゆう",
      "すうじ"
    ],
    "correct": "ほうもん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"法律\"?",
    "word": "法律",
    "options": [
      "みょうじ",
      "ぜったい",
      "ひにく",
      "ほうりつ"
    ],
    "correct": "ほうりつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"保健\"?",
    "word": "保健",
    "options": [
      "ほけん",
      "かいてき",
      "ゆたか",
      "せんでん"
    ],
    "correct": "ほけん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"誇る\"?",
    "word": "誇る",
    "options": [
      "りせい",
      "ほこる",
      "めいれい",
      "じき"
    ],
    "correct": "ほこる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"保証\"?",
    "word": "保証",
    "options": [
      "きんにく",
      "せいちょう",
      "きまり",
      "ほしょう"
    ],
    "correct": "ほしょう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"保存\"?",
    "word": "保存",
    "options": [
      "きょうつう",
      "ほぞん",
      "かわいがる",
      "およぶ"
    ],
    "correct": "ほぞん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"掘る\"?",
    "word": "掘る",
    "options": [
      "しょくば",
      "ほる",
      "こな",
      "ふたん"
    ],
    "correct": "ほる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"満員\"?",
    "word": "満員",
    "options": [
      "まんいん",
      "あつかましい",
      "こうどう",
      "せいり"
    ],
    "correct": "まんいん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"満足\"?",
    "word": "満足",
    "options": [
      "ていあん",
      "ゆうり",
      "よさん",
      "まんぞく"
    ],
    "correct": "まんぞく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"招く\"?",
    "word": "招く",
    "options": [
      "まねく",
      "しゅうしょく",
      "てつ",
      "しんぽ"
    ],
    "correct": "まねく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"迷う\"?",
    "word": "迷う",
    "options": [
      "まよう",
      "あらい",
      "じき",
      "じょうけん"
    ],
    "correct": "まよう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"丸い\"?",
    "word": "丸い",
    "options": [
      "きり",
      "およぶ",
      "むり",
      "まるい"
    ],
    "correct": "まるい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"味方\"?",
    "word": "味方",
    "options": [
      "やとう",
      "ぎょうじ",
      "みかた",
      "このみ"
    ],
    "correct": "みかた"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"見事\"?",
    "word": "見事",
    "options": [
      "たんとう",
      "かがやく",
      "まんぞく",
      "みごと"
    ],
    "correct": "みごと"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"密接\"?",
    "word": "密接",
    "options": [
      "みっせつ",
      "けんきょ",
      "はげしい",
      "けってん"
    ],
    "correct": "みっせつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"密度\"?",
    "word": "密度",
    "options": [
      "こうりゅう",
      "みつど",
      "きおん",
      "なぐさめる"
    ],
    "correct": "みつど"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"導く\"?",
    "word": "導く",
    "options": [
      "ぶんしょう",
      "つうよう",
      "しょうひ",
      "みちびく"
    ],
    "correct": "みちびく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"満ちる\"?",
    "word": "満ちる",
    "options": [
      "みとめる",
      "みちる",
      "へんさい",
      "ふれる"
    ],
    "correct": "みちる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"認める\"?",
    "word": "認める",
    "options": [
      "つうきん",
      "はつめい",
      "こうきゅう",
      "みとめる"
    ],
    "correct": "みとめる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"港\"?",
    "word": "港",
    "options": [
      "うばう",
      "みなと",
      "うやまう",
      "ほうこく"
    ],
    "correct": "みなと"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"未来\"?",
    "word": "未来",
    "options": [
      "よごれ",
      "みりょく",
      "みらい",
      "ゆいいつ"
    ],
    "correct": "みらい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"魅力\"?",
    "word": "魅力",
    "options": [
      "みりょく",
      "くいき",
      "ぶんせき",
      "ちいき"
    ],
    "correct": "みりょく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"民間\"?",
    "word": "民間",
    "options": [
      "しょうじょう",
      "ぶんしょう",
      "さいぜん",
      "みんかん"
    ],
    "correct": "みんかん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"民謡\"?",
    "word": "民謡",
    "options": [
      "のうりつ",
      "はんだん",
      "みんよう",
      "さいのう"
    ],
    "correct": "みんよう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"無線\"?",
    "word": "無線",
    "options": [
      "ごうけい",
      "ゆうり",
      "さばく",
      "むせん"
    ],
    "correct": "むせん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"矛盾\"?",
    "word": "矛盾",
    "options": [
      "むじゅん",
      "せいひん",
      "くべつ",
      "ちょしょ"
    ],
    "correct": "むじゅん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"結ぶ\"?",
    "word": "結ぶ",
    "options": [
      "ようりょう",
      "ととのう",
      "ごうかく",
      "むすぶ"
    ],
    "correct": "むすぶ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"無理\"?",
    "word": "無理",
    "options": [
      "しげき",
      "げんじつ",
      "むり",
      "さつえい"
    ],
    "correct": "むり"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"無料\"?",
    "word": "無料",
    "options": [
      "むりょう",
      "てんけい",
      "かがやく",
      "やくわり"
    ],
    "correct": "むりょう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"明確\"?",
    "word": "明確",
    "options": [
      "ほんやく",
      "めいかく",
      "たいわ",
      "こくさい"
    ],
    "correct": "めいかく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"迷信\"?",
    "word": "迷信",
    "options": [
      "めいしん",
      "すぐれる",
      "かせぐ",
      "ようそ"
    ],
    "correct": "めいしん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"命令\"?",
    "word": "命令",
    "options": [
      "めいれい",
      "しゅうりょう",
      "こうほ",
      "かくじ"
    ],
    "correct": "めいれい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"迷惑\"?",
    "word": "迷惑",
    "options": [
      "めいわく",
      "そうさ",
      "ほうほう",
      "わき"
    ],
    "correct": "めいわく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"恵まれる\"?",
    "word": "恵まれる",
    "options": [
      "かける",
      "じょうほう",
      "めぐまれる",
      "ないよう"
    ],
    "correct": "めぐまれる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"面積\"?",
    "word": "面積",
    "options": [
      "うらむ",
      "にっき",
      "めんせき",
      "きちょう"
    ],
    "correct": "めんせき"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"免税\"?",
    "word": "免税",
    "options": [
      "めんぜい",
      "わん",
      "うらやましい",
      "たいしょく"
    ],
    "correct": "めんぜい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"面倒\"?",
    "word": "面倒",
    "options": [
      "くわしい",
      "やとう",
      "せいじつ",
      "めんどう"
    ],
    "correct": "めんどう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"木材\"?",
    "word": "木材",
    "options": [
      "まんぞく",
      "もくざい",
      "ゆうがい",
      "くんれん"
    ],
    "correct": "もくざい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"目的\"?",
    "word": "目的",
    "options": [
      "はら",
      "もくてき",
      "ふこう",
      "うつる"
    ],
    "correct": "もくてき"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"目標\"?",
    "word": "目標",
    "options": [
      "こうほ",
      "きおく",
      "かのうせい",
      "もくひょう"
    ],
    "correct": "もくひょう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"燃える\"?",
    "word": "燃える",
    "options": [
      "そんざい",
      "やちん",
      "しばふ",
      "もえる"
    ],
    "correct": "もえる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"持ち上げる\"?",
    "word": "持ち上げる",
    "options": [
      "ひかく",
      "かさなる",
      "おさえる",
      "もちあげる"
    ],
    "correct": "もちあげる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"物語\"?",
    "word": "物語",
    "options": [
      "さいじつ",
      "ゆうしょう",
      "ほうこく",
      "ものがたり"
    ],
    "correct": "ものがたり"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"役割\"?",
    "word": "役割",
    "options": [
      "おそれる",
      "さくげん",
      "じじつ",
      "やくわり"
    ],
    "correct": "やくわり"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"家賃\"?",
    "word": "家賃",
    "options": [
      "せきにん",
      "やちん",
      "しゃかい",
      "ていあん"
    ],
    "correct": "やちん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"役立つ\"?",
    "word": "役立つ",
    "options": [
      "やくだつ",
      "ひこう",
      "きょか",
      "さいしん"
    ],
    "correct": "やくだつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"雇う\"?",
    "word": "雇う",
    "options": [
      "やとう",
      "だいひょう",
      "てきとう",
      "ざせき"
    ],
    "correct": "やとう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"破る\"?",
    "word": "破る",
    "options": [
      "わ",
      "やぶる",
      "じき",
      "もくてき"
    ],
    "correct": "やぶる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"唯一\"?",
    "word": "唯一",
    "options": [
      "きたい",
      "つうち",
      "ゆいいつ",
      "くんれん"
    ],
    "correct": "ゆいいつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"優勝\"?",
    "word": "優勝",
    "options": [
      "そしき",
      "ゆうしょう",
      "きろく",
      "くいき"
    ],
    "correct": "ゆうしょう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"優先\"?",
    "word": "優先",
    "options": [
      "せいふ",
      "きょうかい",
      "ゆうせん",
      "てつ"
    ],
    "correct": "ゆうせん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"有害\"?",
    "word": "有害",
    "options": [
      "しま",
      "ゆうがい",
      "かいぜん",
      "はんだん"
    ],
    "correct": "ゆうがい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"有名\"?",
    "word": "有名",
    "options": [
      "はっこう",
      "てんか",
      "ゆうめい",
      "ふきゅう"
    ],
    "correct": "ゆうめい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"幽霊\"?",
    "word": "幽霊",
    "options": [
      "ゆうれい",
      "くろう",
      "くれる",
      "うやまう"
    ],
    "correct": "ゆうれい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"有利\"?",
    "word": "有利",
    "options": [
      "ゆうり",
      "てきとう",
      "かいてき",
      "まさつ"
    ],
    "correct": "ゆうり"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"輸送\"?",
    "word": "輸送",
    "options": [
      "ぶんせき",
      "はんざい",
      "かさなる",
      "ゆそう"
    ],
    "correct": "ゆそう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"譲る\"?",
    "word": "譲る",
    "options": [
      "わるくち",
      "ゆずる",
      "きほん",
      "われわれ"
    ],
    "correct": "ゆずる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"豊か\"?",
    "word": "豊か",
    "options": [
      "きよい",
      "とむ",
      "ひつじゅひん",
      "ゆたか"
    ],
    "correct": "ゆたか"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"輸入\"?",
    "word": "輸入",
    "options": [
      "ゆにゅう",
      "ゆうり",
      "せんしゅ",
      "ふか"
    ],
    "correct": "ゆにゅう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"揺れる\"?",
    "word": "揺れる",
    "options": [
      "ゆれる",
      "きふ",
      "せいちょう",
      "りゅうがく"
    ],
    "correct": "ゆれる"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"余裕\"?",
    "word": "余裕",
    "options": [
      "ぶんけん",
      "げけい",
      "よゆう",
      "ちょきん"
    ],
    "correct": "よゆう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"予言\"?",
    "word": "予言",
    "options": [
      "よげん",
      "ゆれる",
      "はくぶつかん",
      "みょうじ"
    ],
    "correct": "よげん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"予算\"?",
    "word": "予算",
    "options": [
      "ていしゅつ",
      "けいい",
      "よさん",
      "さいしん"
    ],
    "correct": "よさん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"予測\"?",
    "word": "予測",
    "options": [
      "しやくしょ",
      "きちょう",
      "よそく",
      "やとう"
    ],
    "correct": "よそく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"様子\"?",
    "word": "様子",
    "options": [
      "こくふく",
      "さいしょ",
      "よさん",
      "ようす"
    ],
    "correct": "ようす"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"要素\"?",
    "word": "要素",
    "options": [
      "ようそ",
      "うらやましい",
      "わるくち",
      "ひかく"
    ],
    "correct": "ようそ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"容量\"?",
    "word": "容量",
    "options": [
      "うったえる",
      "じゅんきゅう",
      "よごれ",
      "ようりょう"
    ],
    "correct": "ようりょう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"汚れ\"?",
    "word": "汚れ",
    "options": [
      "じゅんきゅう",
      "へんこう",
      "してん",
      "よごれ"
    ],
    "correct": "よごれ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"喜び\"?",
    "word": "喜び",
    "options": [
      "ほうしん",
      "はつめい",
      "よごれる",
      "よろこび"
    ],
    "correct": "よろこび"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"理想\"?",
    "word": "理想",
    "options": [
      "さぎょう",
      "きょうつう",
      "くみあわせ",
      "りそう"
    ],
    "correct": "りそう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"理性\"?",
    "word": "理性",
    "options": [
      "りせい",
      "おしい",
      "してん",
      "ふきん"
    ],
    "correct": "りせい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"利益\"?",
    "word": "利益",
    "options": [
      "めいしょう",
      "りえき",
      "げけい",
      "こんごう"
    ],
    "correct": "りえき"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"理解\"?",
    "word": "理解",
    "options": [
      "きゅうそく",
      "きよい",
      "げんだい",
      "りかい"
    ],
    "correct": "りかい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"陸\"?",
    "word": "陸",
    "options": [
      "りく",
      "やちん",
      "てんねん",
      "ようぼう"
    ],
    "correct": "りく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"離婚\"?",
    "word": "離婚",
    "options": [
      "きょうじゅ",
      "りこん",
      "けってん",
      "もんく"
    ],
    "correct": "りこん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"率\"?",
    "word": "率",
    "options": [
      "りこん",
      "せいのう",
      "しゅうかい",
      "りつ"
    ],
    "correct": "りつ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"留学\"?",
    "word": "留学",
    "options": [
      "きょうりょく",
      "そしき",
      "さそう",
      "りゅうがく"
    ],
    "correct": "りゅうがく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"流行\"?",
    "word": "流行",
    "options": [
      "りゅうこう",
      "おそわる",
      "りそう",
      "つうよう"
    ],
    "correct": "りゅうこう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"量子\"?",
    "word": "量子",
    "options": [
      "りょうし",
      "つごう",
      "どりょく",
      "かみがた"
    ],
    "correct": "りょうし"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"良好\"?",
    "word": "良好",
    "options": [
      "りょうこう",
      "ひとこと",
      "けいい",
      "けんせつ"
    ],
    "correct": "りょうこう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"領土\"?",
    "word": "領土",
    "options": [
      "つなぐ",
      "しゅちょう",
      "ばくはつ",
      "りょうど"
    ],
    "correct": "りょうど"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"緑\"?",
    "word": "緑",
    "options": [
      "みどり",
      "たんとう",
      "せきにん",
      "はっせい"
    ],
    "correct": "みどり"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"類型\"?",
    "word": "類型",
    "options": [
      "まるい",
      "ひょうじょう",
      "ほうもん",
      "るいけい"
    ],
    "correct": "るいけい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"礼儀\"?",
    "word": "礼儀",
    "options": [
      "ていしゅつ",
      "ついか",
      "れいぎ",
      "しげき"
    ],
    "correct": "れいぎ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"冷淡\"?",
    "word": "冷淡",
    "options": [
      "よげん",
      "もちあげる",
      "みどり",
      "れいたん"
    ],
    "correct": "れいたん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"連続\"?",
    "word": "連続",
    "options": [
      "れんぞく",
      "きょか",
      "ていしゅつ",
      "せいり"
    ],
    "correct": "れんぞく"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"老後\"?",
    "word": "老後",
    "options": [
      "ろうご",
      "ごうかく",
      "くべつ",
      "ことば"
    ],
    "correct": "ろうご"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"労働\"?",
    "word": "労働",
    "options": [
      "ぎみ",
      "ろうどう",
      "かける",
      "かくだい"
    ],
    "correct": "ろうどう"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"録音\"?",
    "word": "録音",
    "options": [
      "こし",
      "しゅるい",
      "くろう",
      "ろくおん"
    ],
    "correct": "ろくおん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"論文\"?",
    "word": "論文",
    "options": [
      "ろんぶん",
      "けんそん",
      "にぎる",
      "はったつ"
    ],
    "correct": "ろんぶん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"話題\"?",
    "word": "話題",
    "options": [
      "わだい",
      "どろ",
      "おう",
      "えがく"
    ],
    "correct": "わだい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"我々\"?",
    "word": "我々",
    "options": [
      "つねに",
      "きよい",
      "われわれ",
      "たいけん"
    ],
    "correct": "われわれ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"割引\"?",
    "word": "割引",
    "options": [
      "そうぞう",
      "せいしつ",
      "わりびき",
      "のうみ"
    ],
    "correct": "わりびき"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reading of \"湾\"?",
    "word": "湾",
    "options": [
      "わん",
      "てんじ",
      "のぼる",
      "ていき"
    ],
    "correct": "わん"
  }
]